As	O
a	O
further	O
commitment	O
,	O
IKEA	B-Company
submits	O
an	O
action	O
pledge	O
to	O
accelerate	O
efforts	O
to	O
strengthen	O
child	O
rights	O
in	O
the	O
IKEA	B-Company
supply	O
chain	O
.	O
IKEA	B-Company
MALM	E-ORG
Low	O
Bed	O
Frame	O
Hardware	O
Replacement	O
Parts	O
for	O
Assembling	O
Beds	O
.	O
IKEA	B-Company
(	O
Swedish	S-MISC
:	O
)	O
is	O
a	O
Swedish	S-MISC
founded	O
,	O
Dutch	S-MISC
multinational	O
conglomerate	O
that	O
designs	O
and	O
sells	O
ready-to-assemble	O
furniture	O
,	O
kitchen	O
appliances	O
and	O
home	O
accessories	O
,	O
among	O
other	O
useful	O
goods	O
and	O
occasionally	O
home	O
services	O
.	O
A	I-Company
French	S-MISC
court	O
has	O
ordered	O
IKEA	B-Company
to	O
pay	O
a	O
€	O
1	O
million	O
($	O
1.2	O
million	O
)	O
fine	O
after	O
finding	O
the	O
Swedish	S-MISC
retailer	O
guilty	O
of	O
improperly	O
using	O
employee	O
data	O
.	O
IKEA	B-Company
offers	O
well-designed	O
,	O
functional	O
and	O
affordable	O
,	O
high-quality	O
home	O
furnishing	O
,	O
produced	O
with	O
care	O
for	O
people	O
and	O
the	O
environment	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
several	O
companies	O
with	O
different	O
owners	O
,	O
working	O
under	O
the	O
IKEA	B-Company
Brand	E-ORG
,	O
all	O
sharing	O
the	O
same	O
vision	O
:	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
better	O
everyday	O
life	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
people	O
.	O
IKEA	B-Company
was	O
founded	O
in	O
Sweden	S-LOC
in	O
1943	O
.	O
To	O
create	O
a	O
better	O
everyday	O
life	O
for	O
the	O
many	O
people	O
"	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
IKEA	B-Company
vision	O
.	O
Shop	O
Sears	B-Company
for	O
appliances	O
,	O
tools	O
,	O
clothing	O
,	O
mattresses	O
&	O
more	O
.	O
Manage	O
your	O
Sears	B-Company
credit	O
card	O
account	O
online	O
,	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
using	O
any	O
device	O
.	O
Submit	O
an	O
application	O
for	O
a	I-Company
Sears	B-Company
credit	O
card	O
now	O
.	O
Formerly	O
based	O
at	O
the	O
Sears	B-Company
Tower	E-ORG
in	O
Chicago	S-LOC
and	O
currently	O
headquartered	O
in	O
Hoffman	B-LOC
Estates	E-LOC
,	O
Illinois	S-LOC
,	O
the	O
operation	O
began	O
as	O
a	I-Company
mail	O
ordering	O
catalog	O
company	O
and	O
began	O
...	O
We	O
've	O
directed	O
you	O
to	O
our	O
Sears	B-Company
Category	E-MISC
.	O
Sold	O
by	O
Sears.com	S-ORG
.	O
No	O
matter	O
where	O
you	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
Sears	B-Company
Parts	I-ORG
Direct	E-ORG
has	O
the	O
right	O
parts	O
.	O
Sears	B-Company
Home	I-ORG
Services	E-ORG
is	O
the	O
only	O
nationally	O
authorized	O
appliance	O
repair	O
service	O
for	O
Kenmore	S-ORG
products	O
.	O
Sears	B-Company
-	O
Online	O
&	O
In-Store	O
Shopping	O
:	O
Appliances	O
,	O
Clothing	O
&	O
More	O
Sears	B-Company
base	O
points	O
mean	O
those	O
points	O
awarded	O
as	O
part	O
the	O
standard	O
Shop	B-MISC
Your	I-MISC
Way	E-MISC
program	O
.	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
is	O
the	O
world	O
’s	O
leading	O
provider	O
of	O
open	O
source	O
solutions	O
,	O
using	O
a	I-Company
community-powered	O
approach	O
to	O
provide	O
reliable	O
and	O
high-performing	O
cloud	O
,	O
virtualization	O
,	O
storage	O
,	O
Linux	S-MISC
,	O
and	O
middleware	O
technologies	O
.	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
also	O
offers	O
award-winning	O
support	O
,	O
training	O
,	O
and	O
consulting	O
services	O
.	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
is	O
an	O
S	B-MISC
&	I-MISC
P	I-MISC
500	E-MISC
company	O
with	O
more	O
than	O
80	O
offices	O
spanning	O
the	O
globe	O
,	O
empowering	O
its	O
customers	O
...	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
multinational	O
software	O
company	O
that	O
provides	O
open	O
source	O
software	O
products	O
to	O
enterprises	O
.	O
Founded	O
in	O
1993	O
,	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
has	O
its	O
corporate	O
headquarters	O
in	O
Raleigh	S-LOC
,	O
North	B-LOC
Carolina	E-LOC
,	O
with	O
other	O
offices	O
worldwide	O
.	O
It	O
became	O
a	I-Company
subsidiary	O
of	O
IBM	S-ORG
on	O
July	O
9	O
,	O
2019.	O
.	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
has	O
become	O
associated	O
to	O
a	I-Company
large	O
extent	O
with	O
its	O
enterprise	O
operating	O
system	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
Enterprise	I-MISC
Linux	E-MISC
.	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
Enterprise	I-ORG
Linux	E-ORG
(	O
RHEL	S-ORG
)	O
is	O
a	I-Company
paid	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
product	O
that	O
includes	O
support	O
directly	O
from	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
.	O
A	O
typical	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
Enterprise	I-MISC
Linux	E-MISC
includes	O
several	O
applications	O
,	O
development	O
tools	O
and	O
utilities	O
such	O
as	O
Samba	S-ORG
,	O
OpenOffice.org	S-MISC
,	O
MySQL	S-MISC
,	O
GIMP	S-ORG
,	O
Firefox	S-ORG
...	O
The	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
Society	E-ORG
is	O
a	I-Company
playgroup	O
for	O
women	O
created	O
to	O
connect	O
like-minded	O
women	O
,	O
make	O
new	O
friends	O
and	O
enrich	O
lives	O
through	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
fun	O
and	O
friendship	O
!	O
The	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
Society	E-ORG
(	O
RHS	S-ORG
)	O
is	O
an	O
international	O
social	O
organization	O
that	O
was	O
founded	O
in	O
1998	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
for	O
women	O
age	O
50	O
and	O
beyond	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
open	O
to	O
women	O
of	O
all	O
ages	O
.	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
offers	O
free	O
services	O
to	O
churches	O
schools	O
and	O
civic	O
organizations	O
that	O
would	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
auction	O
as	O
a	I-Company
fundraiser	O
.	O
Red	B-Company
Hat	I-Company
Realty	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Auction	E-ORG
is	O
a	I-Company
full	O
service	O
corporation	O
with	O
16	O
qualified	O
independent	O
contractors	O
and	O
service	O
personnel	O
.	O
The	O
University	B-Company
of	I-Company
Chicago	I-Company
offers	O
a	I-Company
robust	O
collection	O
of	I-Company
virtual	O
resources	O
to	O
help	O
prospective	O
students	O
prepare	O
for	O
the	O
college	O
application	O
journey	O
.	O
University	B-Company
of	I-Company
Chicago	I-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
private	O
institution	O
that	O
was	O
founded	O
in	O
1890	O
.	O
University	B-Company
of	I-Company
Chicago	I-Company
Rankings	E-ORG
.	O
The	O
University	B-Company
of	I-Company
Chicago	I-Company
.	O
Recognized	O
as	O
one	O
of	I-Company
the	O
most	O
prestigious	O
and	O
academically	O
rigorous	O
universities	O
in	O
the	O
nation	O
,	O
the	O
University	B-Company
of	I-Company
Chicago	I-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
small	O
research	O
institute	O
responsible	O
for	O
producing	O
many	O
of	I-Company
the	O
...	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
combines	O
luxury	O
with	O
performance	O
across	O
the	O
full	O
line	O
of	O
models	O
including	O
luxury	O
sedans	O
,	O
SUVs	O
,	O
coupes	O
,	O
roadsters	O
,	O
convertibles	O
&	O
more	O
.	O
Exclusive	O
reports	O
and	O
current	O
films	O
:	O
experience	O
a	O
broad	O
range	O
of	O
topics	O
from	O
the	O
fascinating	O
world	O
of	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
.	O
To	O
find	O
out	O
about	O
offers	O
in	O
your	O
location	O
,	O
please	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
local	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
website	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
International	O
website	O
of	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
AG	E-ORG
.	O
The	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
V-Class	E-MISC
combines	O
comfort	O
and	O
luxury	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
scale	O
.	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
AMG	I-MISC
GT	E-MISC
63	O
.	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
AMG	E-ORG
S	O
63	O
.	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
AMG	I-MISC
SLC	E-MISC
43	O
.	O
The	O
finest	O
new	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
dealer	O
serving	O
Denver	S-LOC
,	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
of	O
Littleton	S-LOC
is	O
ready	O
to	O
help	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
perfect	O
luxury	O
vehicle	O
.	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
Dealer	O
Serving	O
Nashville	S-LOC
,	O
TN	S-LOC
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
the	O
official	O
homepage	O
of	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
of	O
Nashville	S-LOC
.	O
We	O
are	O
Music	B-LOC
City	E-LOC
's	O
country	O
star	O
world-class	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
dealer	O
.	O
Among	O
car	O
brands	O
,	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
prestigious	O
and	O
recognized	O
names	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
of	O
Coral	B-LOC
Gables	E-LOC
is	O
a	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
dealership	O
located	O
near	O
Coral	B-LOC
Gables	I-LOC
Florida	E-LOC
.	O
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
of	O
South	B-LOC
Charlotte	E-LOC
.	O
When	O
you	O
choose	O
Felix	B-MISC
Sabates'	I-MISC
Mercedes-Benz	B-Company
of	O
South	B-LOC
Charlotte	E-LOC
to	O
meet	O
your	O
high-end	O
automotive	O
needs	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
getting	O
an	O
entire	O
team	O
of	O
dedicated	O
automotive	O
professionals	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
the	O
official	O
website	O
for	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
,	O
creator	O
of	I-Company
Assassin	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Creed	E-ORG
,	O
Just	B-MISC
Dance	E-MISC
,	O
Tom	B-PER
Clancy	E-PER
's	O
video	O
game	O
series	O
,	O
Rayman	B-MISC
,	I-MISC
Far	I-MISC
Cry	E-MISC
,	O
Watch	B-MISC
Dogs	E-MISC
and	O
many	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
Store	E-ORG
features	O
the	O
best	O
adventures	O
on	O
PC	O
,	O
PS4	S-MISC
,	O
Xbox	B-MISC
One	E-MISC
and	O
Switch	S-MISC
:	O
become	O
a	O
viking	O
legend	O
in	O
Assassin	B-MISC
's	I-MISC
Creed	I-MISC
Valhalla	E-MISC
,	O
fight	O
for	O
freedom	O
in	O
Far	B-MISC
Cry	I-MISC
6	E-MISC
,	O
or	O
join	O
the	O
Special	B-ORG
Forces	E-ORG
with	O
Rainbow	B-MISC
Six	I-MISC
Siege	E-MISC
.	O
Connect	O
with	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
players	O
,	O
enjoy	O
Rewards	O
and	O
discounts	O
,	O
compare	O
your	O
stats	O
with	O
your	O
friends	O
and	O
much	O
more	O
in	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
Connect	E-ORG
.	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
+	O
.	O
By	O
continuing	O
to	O
navigate	O
on	O
this	O
site	O
,	O
you	O
accept	O
the	O
use	O
of	I-Company
cookies	O
by	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
and	O
its	O
partners	O
to	O
offer	O
advertising	O
adapted	O
to	O
your	O
interests	O
,	O
collect	O
visit	O
statistics	O
and	O
allow	O
you	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
social	O
network	O
share	O
buttons	O
.	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
Entertainment	I-ORG
SA	E-ORG
(/	O
ˈ	O
j	O
uː	O
b	I-Company
i	I-Company
s	I-Company
ɒ	O
f	I-Company
t	I-Company
,-	O
s	I-Company
ɔː	O
f	I-Company
t	I-Company
/	O
;	O
French	S-MISC
:	O
;	O
formerly	O
Ubi	I-Company
Soft	I-ORG
Entertainment	I-ORG
SA	E-ORG
)	O
is	I-Company
a	O
French	S-MISC
video	O
game	O
company	O
headquartered	O
in	O
the	O
Montreuil	S-LOC
suburb	O
of	I-Company
Paris	S-LOC
with	O
several	O
development	O
studios	O
across	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
One	O
discounted	O
month	O
per	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
Account	E-ORG
from	O
3rd	O
June	O
2021	O
to	O
22nd	O
June	O
2021	O
(	O
8	O
am	O
PST	O
/	O
12	O
pm	O
EDT	O
)	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
end	O
of	I-Company
the	O
discounted	O
month	O
,	O
Ubisoft	B-Company
+	O
will	O
automatically	O
renew	O
and	O
the	O
payment	O
method	O
provided	O
at	O
checkout	O
will	O
be	O
charged	O
$	O
14.99	O
/	O
month	O
until	O
you	O
cancel	O
,	O
by	O
following	O
the	O
instructions	O
on	O
ubisoftplus.com	S-MISC
.	O
The	O
Library	B-Company
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
is	O
the	O
nation	O
's	O
oldest	O
federal	O
cultural	O
institution	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
serves	O
as	O
the	O
research	O
arm	O
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
.	O
Presented	O
by	O
the	O
Library	B-Company
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
,	O
Congress.gov	S-ORG
is	O
the	O
official	O
website	O
for	O
U.S.	S-LOC
federal	O
legislative	O
information	O
.	O
Library	B-Company
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
.	O
The	O
Library	B-Company
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
provides	O
Congress	I-Company
with	O
objective	O
research	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
legislative	O
process	O
,	O
administers	O
the	O
national	O
copyright	O
system	O
,	O
and	O
manages	O
the	O
largest	O
collection	O
of	I-Company
books	O
,	O
recordings	O
,	O
photographs	O
,	O
maps	O
and	O
manuscripts	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Databases	O
(	O
Library	B-Company
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
Electronic	I-ORG
Resources	I-ORG
Online	I-ORG
Catalog	E-ORG
)	O
.	O
The	O
Library	B-Company
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
is	O
making	O
every	O
effort	O
to	O
make	O
its	O
online	O
collections	O
and	O
information	O
available	O
to	O
all	O
members	O
of	I-Company
the	O
public	O
.	O
The	O
Library	B-Company
of	I-Company
Congress	I-Company
is	O
housed	O
across	O
three	O
buildings	O
on	I-Company
Capitol	B-LOC
Hill	E-LOC
in	O
Washington	S-LOC
,	O
DC	S-LOC
:	O
the	O
Thomas	B-ORG
Jefferson	I-ORG
Building	E-ORG
(	O
10	O
1st	B-ORG
Street	I-ORG
SE	E-ORG
)	O
,	O
the	O
James	B-ORG
Madison	I-ORG
Memorial	I-ORG
Building	E-ORG
(	O
101	O
Independence	B-ORG
Avenue	I-ORG
SE	E-ORG
)	O
and	O
the	O
John	B-ORG
Adams	I-ORG
Building	E-ORG
(	O
2nd	B-LOC
Street	I-LOC
SE	E-LOC
,	O
between	O
Independence	B-LOC
Avenue	E-LOC
and	O
East	B-LOC
Capitol	I-LOC
Street	E-LOC
)	O
.	O
Our	O
Museums	O
,	O
Galleries	O
,	O
and	O
Zoo	O
|	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
Our	I-ORG
Museums	E-ORG
,	O
Galleries	O
,	O
and	O
Zoo	O
19	O
world-class	O
museums	O
,	O
galleries	O
,	O
gardens	O
,	O
and	O
a	I-Company
zoo	O
As	O
we	O
gradually	O
reopen	O
the	O
museums	O
,	O
we	O
’re	O
putting	O
safety	O
first	O
and	O
requiring	O
free	O
timed-entry	O
passes	O
.	O
The	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
(/	O
s	I-Company
m	I-Company
ɪ	O
θ	O
ˈ	O
s	I-Company
oʊ	O
n	I-Company
i	I-Company
ə	O
n	I-Company
/	O
smith-SOH-nee-ən	O
)	O
,	O
also	O
known	O
simply	O
as	O
The	B-ORG
Smithsonian	B-Company
,	O
is	O
a	I-Company
trust	O
instrumentality	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
composed	O
as	O
a	I-Company
group	O
of	O
museums	O
and	O
research	O
centers	O
.	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Museums	E-ORG
in	O
Washington	S-LOC
,	O
DC	S-LOC
Collectively	O
called	O
the	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
,	O
this	O
world-renowned	O
museum	O
and	O
research	O
complex	O
consists	O
of	O
17	O
museums	O
,	O
galleries	O
and	O
a	I-Company
zoo	O
.	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
The	I-ORG
Smithsonian	B-Company
is	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
largest	O
museum	O
and	O
research	O
complex	O
,	O
with	O
19	O
museums	O
and	O
galleries	O
,	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Zoo	E-ORG
,	O
and	O
9	O
research	O
facilities	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
?	O
Collectively	O
called	O
the	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
,	O
the	O
world-renowned	O
museum	O
and	O
research	O
complex	O
consists	O
of	O
17	O
museums	O
and	O
galleries	O
in	O
Washington	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
DC	E-LOC
,	O
including	O
the	O
National	B-ORG
Zoo	E-ORG
.	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
,	O
research	O
institution	O
founded	O
by	O
the	O
bequest	O
of	O
James	B-PER
Smithson	I-Company
,	O
an	I-Company
English	S-MISC
scientist	O
.	O
Smithson	I-Company
,	O
who	O
died	O
in	O
1829	O
,	O
had	O
stipulated	O
in	O
his	O
will	O
that	O
should	O
his	O
nephew	O
and	O
heir	O
himself	O
die	O
without	O
issue	O
,	O
his	O
remaining	O
assets	O
would	O
pass	O
to	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
and	O
be	O
used	O
to	O
found	O
the	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	I-Company
.	O
Founded	O
in	O
1971	O
,	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
leading	O
entertainment	O
companies	O
and	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
legendary	O
Star	B-ORG
Wars	E-ORG
and	O
Indiana	B-ORG
Jones	E-ORG
franchises	O
.	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Ltd	I-ORG
.	I-ORG
Learn	B-MISC
the	I-MISC
Story	I-MISC
of	I-MISC
the	I-MISC
Tuskegee	I-MISC
Airmen	E-MISC
at	O
Lucasfilm.com	S-MISC
.	O
The	O
acclaimed	O
documentary	O
Double	B-MISC
Victory	E-MISC
,	O
the	O
film	I-Company
Red	B-MISC
Tails	E-MISC
,	O
and	O
all-new	O
educational	O
resources	O
celebrating	O
these	O
unsung	O
heroes	O
of	O
World	B-MISC
War	I-MISC
II	E-MISC
are	O
now	O
available	O
on	O
the	O
official	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
website	O
.	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
NOVEMBER	O
11	O
,	O
2020	O
.	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
was	O
founded	O
by	O
filmmaker	O
George	B-PER
Lucas	I-Company
in	O
1971.Lucas	S-ORG
served	O
as	I-Company
the	O
company	O
's	O
chairman	O
and	O
CEO	O
until	O
2012.	O
.	O
On	O
July	O
8	O
,	O
2005	O
,	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
's	O
marketing	O
,	O
online	O
,	O
and	O
licensing	O
units	O
moved	O
into	O
the	O
new	O
Letterman	B-ORG
Digital	I-ORG
Arts	I-ORG
Center	E-ORG
located	O
in	O
the	O
Presidio	S-LOC
in	O
San	B-LOC
Francisco	E-LOC
.	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
//	O
DECEMBER	O
10	O
,	O
2020	O
.	O
Future	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Projects	I-MISC
Revealed	I-MISC
Get	E-MISC
ready	O
for	O
Patty	B-MISC
Jenkins’	I-MISC
Rogue	I-MISC
Squadron	E-MISC
film	I-Company
,	O
an	O
Ahsoka	B-MISC
Tano	E-MISC
live-action	O
series	O
,	O
the	O
return	O
of	O
Hayden	B-PER
Christensen	E-PER
and	O
much	O
,	O
much	O
more	O
.	O
Today	O
at	O
The	B-ORG
Walt	I-ORG
Disney	I-ORG
Company	E-ORG
’s	O
Investor	B-MISC
Day	E-MISC
event	O
,	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
president	O
Kathleen	B-PER
Kennedy	E-PER
announced	O
a	I-Company
staggering	O
number	O
of	O
new	O
films	O
,	O
series	O
,	O
and	O
surprises	O
that	O
will	O
expand	O
the	O
Star	B-MISC
...	E-MISC
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Ltd	E-ORG
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	I-Company
subsidiary	O
of	O
The	B-ORG
Walt	I-ORG
Disney	I-ORG
Company	E-ORG
,	O
following	O
Disney	S-ORG
's	O
October	O
2012	O
purchase	O
of	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
.	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
.	O
This	O
made	O
it	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
's	O
first	O
ever	O
prequel	O
movie	O
when	O
it	O
opened	O
in	O
theaters	O
in	O
1984	O
.	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
headquarters	O
,	O
yes	O
The	B-ORG
Lucasfilm	B-Company
,	O
is	O
located	O
inside	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
many	O
campuses	O
in	O
the	O
Presidio	S-LOC
.	O
The	O
latest	O
tweets	O
from	O
@	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
_	O
Ltd	S-ORG
Met	I-Company
Express	O
:	O
Highlights	O
of	I-Company
the	O
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
in	O
2	O
Hours	O
(	O
From	O
$	O
52.00	O
)	O
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
Private	O
Guided	O
Tour	O
with	O
Skip-the-Line	O
Ticket	O
(	O
From	O
$	O
100.70	O
)	O
Highlights	O
of	I-Company
the	O
Met	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
Tour	E-MISC
(	O
From	O
$	O
94.69	O
)	O
See	O
all	O
The	B-ORG
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
experiences	O
on	O
Tripadvisor	S-ORG
The	O
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
of	I-Company
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
City	E-LOC
,	O
colloquially	O
"	O
the	O
Met	I-Company
,"	O
is	O
the	O
largest	O
art	O
museum	O
in	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
.	O
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
,	O
byname	O
the	O
Met	I-Company
,	O
the	O
largest	O
and	O
most-comprehensive	O
art	O
museum	O
in	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
City	E-LOC
and	O
one	O
of	I-Company
the	O
foremost	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
The	O
Met	I-Company
Store	O
|	O
Gifts	O
from	O
The	B-ORG
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
As	O
the	O
new	O
director	O
of	I-Company
the	O
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
makes	O
his	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
museum	O
and	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
Art	I-Company
News	E-ORG
interviews	O
friends	O
and	O
colleagues	O
of	I-Company
Max	B-PER
Hollein	E-PER
about	O
his	O
professional	O
and	O
personal	O
style	O
.	O
Follow	O
the	O
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
.	O
Virtually	O
explore	O
Metropolitan	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
in	O
a	I-Company
fully	O
immersive	O
360-degree	O
experience	O
.	O
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
sold	O
several	O
hundred	O
million	O
coronavirus	S-MISC
test	O
kits	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
which	O
helped	O
keep	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
revenue	O
and	O
earnings	O
afloat	O
.	O
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
multinational	O
medical	O
devices	O
and	O
health	O
care	O
company	O
with	O
headquarters	O
in	O
Abbott	B-Company
Park	E-LOC
,	O
Illinois	S-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
.	O
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
cuts	O
2021	O
adj	O
.	O
Careers	O
at	I-Company
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
|	O
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
Jobs	E-ORG
.	O
-.	O
-	O
.	O
No	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
Abbott	B-Company
trademark	O
,	O
trade	O
name	O
,	O
or	I-Company
trade	O
dress	O
in	O
this	O
site	O
may	O
be	O
made	O
without	O
the	O
prior	O
written	O
authorization	O
of	O
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
,	O
except	O
to	I-Company
identify	O
the	O
product	O
or	I-Company
services	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
.	O
The	O
average	O
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
salary	O
ranges	O
from	O
approximately	O
$	O
30,000	O
per	O
year	O
for	O
Bilingual	O
Customer	O
Service	O
Associate	O
to	I-Company
$	O
138,406	O
per	O
year	O
for	O
Senior	O
Territory	O
Manager	O
.	O
Average	O
Abbott	B-Company
Laboratories	I-Company
hourly	O
pay	O
ranges	O
from	O
approximately	O
$	O
13.32	O
per	O
hour	O
for	O
Inspector	O
to	I-Company
$	O
50.00	O
per	O
hour	O
for	O
Software	O
Architect	O
.	O
Netflix	S-ORG
and	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
Sign	I-MISC
Pay-One	I-MISC
U.S.	I-MISC
Licensing	I-MISC
Deal	I-MISC
for	I-MISC
Feature	I-MISC
Films	E-MISC
April	O
8	O
,	O
2021	O
Hollywood	S-LOC
,	O
Calif.	S-LOC
,	O
April	O
8	O
,	O
2021	O
--	O
Netflix	S-ORG
and	O
Sony	B-Company
Picture	I-Company
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
Inc	E-ORG
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
the	O
official	O
channel	O
for	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
and	O
Amazon	B-ORG
Falls	E-ORG
to	O
Open	B-ORG
World	E-ORG
’s	O
First	B-ORG
Columbia	I-ORG
Pictures	I-Company
Theme	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Waterpark	E-ORG
in	I-Company
Thailand	S-LOC
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
Names	O
Ravi	B-ORG
Ahuja	E-ORG
Chairman	O
,	O
Global	B-ORG
Television	I-ORG
Studios	E-ORG
and	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
Corporate	I-ORG
Development	E-ORG
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
Principles	E-ORG
.	O
Convocation	O
|	O
The	B-Company
University	I-Company
of	I-Company
Chicago	I-Company
.	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Ltd	I-Company
.	I-Company
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Ltd	I-Company
.	I-Company
LLC	I-Company
operates	O
as	I-Company
a	I-Company
film	I-Company
and	O
entertainment	O
company	O
.	I-Company
Ren	B-ORG
Ventures	I-ORG
Ltd	I-Company
.	I-Company
et	O
al	O
v	O
.	I-Company
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Ltd	I-Company
.	I-Company
LLC	I-Company
et	O
al	B-ORG
California	I-ORG
Northern	I-ORG
District	I-ORG
Court	E-ORG
-	O
April	O
23	O
,	O
2018	O
Hilsley	S-ORG
v	O
.	I-Company
General	B-ORG
Mills	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc	E-ORG
.	I-Company
et	O
al	B-ORG
California	I-ORG
Southern	I-ORG
District	I-ORG
Court	E-ORG
-	O
February	O
21	O
,	O
2018	O
VidAngel	S-ORG
v	O
.	I-Company
Disney	B-ORG
Enterprises	E-ORG
et	O
al	B-ORG
Utah	I-ORG
District	I-ORG
Court	E-ORG
-	O
February	O
16	O
,	O
2018	O
...	O
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Ltd	I-Company
.	I-Company
LLC	I-Company
,	O
an	O
entertainment	O
service	O
company	O
,	O
produces	O
original	O
content	O
,	O
postproduction	O
effects	O
,	O
and	O
audio	O
for	O
external	O
clients	O
,	O
licensed	O
products	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gaming	O
industry	O
.	I-Company
Lucasfilm	B-Company
Ltd	I-Company
.	I-Company
LLC	I-Company
.	I-Company
It	O
is	O
considered	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
big	O
four	O
Internet	S-MISC
stocks	O
along	O
with	O
Amazon	S-ORG
,	O
Facebook	S-ORG
,	O
and	O
Apple.	S-ORG
.	O
Google	B-Company
was	O
founded	O
in	O
September	O
1998	O
by	O
Larry	B-PER
Page	E-PER
and	O
Sergey	B-PER
Brin	E-PER
while	O
they	O
...	O
The	O
latest	O
Tweets	O
from	O
Google	B-Company
(@	O
Google	B-Company
)	O
.	O
#	O
HeyGoogle	S-ORG
.	O
Google	B-Company
Scholar	E-ORG
provides	O
a	O
simple	O
way	O
to	O
broadly	O
search	O
for	O
scholarly	O
literature	O
.	O
Operating	O
across	O
four	O
business	O
sectors	O
–	O
Mobility	B-ORG
Solutions	E-ORG
,	O
Industrial	O
Technology	O
,	O
Consumer	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Energy	O
and	O
Building	O
Technology	O
–	O
Bosch	B-Company
is	O
uniquely	O
positioned	O
to	O
offer	O
customers	O
a	O
multitude	O
of	O
value-add	O
,	O
cross-sector	O
solutions	O
across	O
a	O
diversity	O
of	O
industry	O
applications	O
.	O
Bosch	B-Company
:	O
Created	O
by	O
Eric	B-PER
Ellis	I-PER
Overmyer	E-PER
.	O
Bosch	B-Company
has	O
been	O
designing	O
home	O
and	O
kitchen	O
appliances	O
for	O
over	O
125	O
years	O
,	O
consistently	O
raising	O
the	O
standards	O
in	O
quietness	O
,	O
efficiency	O
and	O
integrated	O
design	O
.	O
Experience	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
"	O
invented	O
for	O
life	O
"	O
by	O
Bosch	B-Company
completely	O
new	O
.	O
Bosch	B-Company
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
police	O
procedural	O
streaming	O
television	O
series	O
produced	O
by	O
Amazon	B-ORG
Studios	E-ORG
and	O
Fabrik	B-ORG
Entertainment	E-ORG
starring	O
Titus	B-PER
Welliver	E-PER
as	O
Los	B-ORG
Angeles	I-ORG
Police	E-ORG
detective	O
Harry	B-PER
Bosch	B-Company
.	O
Bosch	B-Company
PRO	O
+	O
GUARD	O
™	O
dust	O
solutions	O
are	O
designed	O
to	O
help	O
you	O
move	O
toward	O
compliance	O
with	O
the	O
OSHA	S-ORG
silica	O
dust	O
regulation	O
.	O
An	O
example	O
is	O
that	O
Bosch	B-Company
dust	O
extractors	O
keep	O
the	O
air	O
cleaner	O
by	O
using	O
HEPA	O
filters	O
that	O
capture	O
99.97	O
percent	O
of	O
dust	O
particles	O
.	O
The	O
Bosch	B-Company
Group	E-ORG
is	O
a	O
leading	O
global	O
supplier	O
of	O
technology	O
and	O
services	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
automotive	O
area	O
,	O
Bosch	B-Company
is	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
original	O
equipment	O
and	O
innovation	O
leader	O
,	O
manufacturing	O
and	O
marketing	O
original	O
equipment	O
and	O
aftermarket	O
products	O
for	O
the	O
North	B-MISC
American	E-MISC
The	B-Company
Criterion	I-Company
Collection	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc	E-ORG
.	O
(	O
or	O
simply	O
Criterion	I-Company
)	O
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
home	O
video	O
distribution	O
company	O
that	O
focuses	O
on	I-Company
licensing	O
"	O
important	O
classic	O
and	O
contemporary	O
films	O
"	O
.	O
The	B-Company
Criterion	I-Company
Collection	I-Company
is	O
a	O
collection	O
of	O
outstanding	O
films	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
given	O
special	O
treatment	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
restoration	O
,	O
commentary	O
,	O
additional	O
materials	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
The	B-Company
Irishman	S-MISC
(	O
The	B-Company
Criterion	I-Company
Collection	I-Company
)	O
by	O
Robert	B-PER
De	I-PER
Niro	E-PER
.	O
The	O
covers	O
of	O
several	O
issues	O
of	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
magazine	O
.	O
Predating	O
the	O
video	O
game	O
company	O
,	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
was	O
a	I-Company
self	O
...	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
Inc	E-ORG
.	O
(	O
JP	S-ORG
:)	O
(	O
CN	O
)	O
is	O
a	I-Company
video	O
game	O
developer	O
based	O
in	O
Japan	S-LOC
.	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
jointly	O
owns	O
The	B-ORG
Pokémon	I-ORG
Company	E-ORG
alongside	O
Nintendo	S-ORG
and	O
Creatures.	S-ORG
.	O
History	O
.	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
was	O
originally	O
a	I-Company
self-published	O
gaming	O
magazine	O
created	O
by	O
Satoshi	B-PER
Tajiri	E-PER
and	O
Ken	B-PER
Sugimori	E-PER
in	O
...	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc	E-ORG
(株式(かぶしき)会社(がいしゃ)ゲ	O
ー	O
ムフリ	O
ー	O
ク	O
Kabushiki-gaisha	B-PER
Geemu	I-PER
Furiiku	E-PER
)	O
is	O
a	I-Company
Japanese	S-MISC
video	O
game	O
developer	O
,	O
established	O
April	O
26	O
,	O
1989	O
.	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc	E-ORG
.	O
(	O
Japanese	S-MISC
:	O
株式会社ゲ	O
ー	O
ムフリ	O
ー	O
ク	O
Kabushiki	B-MISC
gaisha	I-MISC
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
)	O
,	O
officially	O
stylized	O
as	O
GAME	O
FREAK	O
inc	O
.	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
is	O
responsible	O
for	O
the	O
development	O
of	O
the	O
core	O
series	O
Pokémon	S-MISC
games	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
free-to-play	O
...	O
The	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
logo	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	I-Company
blobby	O
black	O
circle	O
with	O
a	I-Company
"	O
G	I-Company
"	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
appears	O
with	O
"	O
GAME	O
FREAK	O
"	O
written	O
below	O
.	O
2nd	O
logo	O
:	O
On	O
a	I-Company
black	O
background	O
,	O
the	O
Game	B-Company
Freak	I-Company
logo	O
appears	O
.	O
Robert	B-Company
Bosch	I-Company
GmbH	I-Company
.	O
Robert	B-Company
Bosch	I-Company
Gesellschaft	E-ORG
mit	O
beschraenkter	B-ORG
Haftung	E-ORG
manufacture	O
auto	O
parts	O
.	O
Robert	B-Company
Bosch	I-Company
(	O
23	O
September	O
1861	O
–	O
12	O
March	O
1942	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
German	S-MISC
industrialist	O
,	O
engineer	O
and	O
inventor	O
,	O
founder	O
of	O
Robert	B-Company
Bosch	I-Company
GmbH	I-Company
.	O
Biography	O
.	O
NASA.gov	S-MISC
brings	O
you	O
the	O
latest	O
news	O
,	O
images	O
and	O
videos	O
from	O
America	S-LOC
's	O
space	O
agency	O
,	O
pioneering	O
the	O
future	O
in	O
space	O
exploration	O
,	O
scientific	O
discovery	O
and	O
aeronautics	O
research	O
.	O
The	O
NASA	B-Company
seal	O
was	O
approved	O
by	O
Eisenhower	S-PER
in	O
1959	O
,	O
and	O
slightly	O
modified	O
by	O
President	O
John	B-PER
F.	I-PER
Kennedy	E-PER
in	O
1961	O
.	O
NASA	B-Company
's	O
first	O
logo	O
was	O
designed	O
by	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
Lewis'	B-ORG
Research	I-ORG
Reports	I-ORG
Division	E-ORG
,	O
James	B-PER
Modarelli	E-PER
,	O
as	O
a	O
simplification	O
of	O
the	O
1959	O
seal	O
.	O
NASA	B-Company
’s	O
real-time	O
portal	O
for	O
Mars	S-ORG
exploration	O
,	O
featuring	O
the	O
latest	O
news	O
,	O
images	O
,	O
and	O
discoveries	O
from	O
the	O
Red	B-MISC
Planet	E-MISC
.	O
NASA	B-Company
’s	O
Climate	B-ORG
Kids	E-ORG
website	O
brings	O
the	O
exciting	O
science	O
of	O
climate	O
change	O
and	O
sustainability	O
to	O
life	O
,	O
providing	O
clear	O
explanations	O
for	O
the	O
big	O
questions	O
in	O
climate	O
science	O
.	O
Delta	B-Company
Air	I-Company
Lines	I-Company
.	O
Delta	B-Company
Air	I-Company
Lines	I-Company
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
largest	O
air	O
carriers	O
.	O
Delta	B-Company
Air	I-Company
Lines	I-Company
(	O
NYSE	S-ORG
:	O
DAL	S-ORG
)	O
is	O
the	O
U.S.	S-LOC
global	O
airline	O
leader	O
in	I-Company
products	O
,	O
services	O
,	O
innovation	O
,	O
reliability	O
and	O
customer	O
experience	O
.	O
Delta	B-Company
Air	I-Company
Lines	I-Company
,	O
Inc	B-ORG
Size	E-ORG
188.3	O
MB	O
.	O
An	O
off-duty	O
Delta	B-Company
Air	I-Company
Lines	I-Company
flight	O
attendant	O
apparently	O
commandeered	O
the	O
intercom	O
on	O
an	O
Atlanta-bound	S-MISC
flight	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
leading	O
to	O
a	I-Company
scuffle	O
that	O
forced	O
the	O
plane	O
to	O
land	O
in	I-Company
Oklahoma	B-LOC
City	E-LOC
,	O
an	O
...	O
Delta	B-Company
Air	I-Company
Lines	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
or	O
just	O
Delta	B-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
large	O
airline	O
.	O
Discover	O
our	O
menu	O
and	O
order	O
delivery	O
or	O
pick	O
up	O
from	O
a	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
near	O
you	O
.	O
Discover	O
our	O
menu	O
and	O
order	O
delivery	O
or	O
pick	O
up	O
from	O
a	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
near	O
you	O
.	O
After	O
Insta-Burger	B-ORG
King	I-Company
ran	O
into	O
financial	O
difficulties	O
in	I-Company
1954	O
,	O
its	O
two	O
Miami-based	S-MISC
franchisees	O
David	B-PER
Edgerton	E-PER
and	O
James	B-PER
McLamore	E-PER
purchased	O
the	O
company	O
and	O
...	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
(	O
BK	S-ORG
)	O
is	O
a	O
global	O
fast-food	O
chain	O
that	O
began	O
operating	O
in	I-Company
1953	O
and	O
currently	O
has	O
over	O
15,000	O
locations	O
.	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
calories	O
are	O
on	O
the	O
higher	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
spectrum	O
and	O
need	O
to	O
be	O
considered	O
to	O
maintain	O
a	O
balanced	O
diet	O
.	O
With	O
the	O
free	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
App	E-MISC
,	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
customize	O
every	O
order	O
.	O
Plus	O
,	O
the	O
app	O
allows	O
you	O
to	O
:	O
Locate	O
your	O
nearest	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
restaurant	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
.	O
(	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
is	O
one	O
of	O
America	S-LOC
’s	O
favorite	O
fast	O
food	O
restaurants	O
;	O
their	O
signature	O
menu	O
item	O
is	O
the	O
flame	O
grilled	O
Whopper	O
sandwich	O
which	O
.	O
Burger	B-Company
King	I-Company
.	O
(	O
Barnes	B-Company
&	I-Company
Noble	I-Company
’s	O
online	O
bookstore	O
for	O
books	O
,	O
NOOK	O
ebooks	O
&	I-Company
magazines	O
.	O
Receive	O
free	O
shipping	O
with	O
your	O
Barnes	B-Company
&	I-Company
Noble	I-Company
Membership	E-ORG
.	O
Barnes	B-Company
&	I-Company
Noble	I-Company
–	O
shop	O
books	O
Books	O
More	O
ways	O
to	O
shop	O
:	O
Find	O
an	O
Apple	B-ORG
Store	E-ORG
or	O
other	O
retailer	O
near	O
you	O
.	O
Barnes	B-Company
&	I-Company
Noble	I-Company
is	O
the	O
world	O
’s	O
largest	O
bookseller	O
,	O
and	O
a	I-Company
leading	O
retailer	O
of	O
content	O
and	O
educational	O
products	O
.	O
Book	O
Store	O
in	O
Gaithersburg	S-LOC
,	O
MD	S-LOC
|	O
Barnes	B-Company
&	I-Company
Noble	I-Company
Tuesday	O
June	O
22	O
,	O
2021	O
7:00	O
PM	O
Join	O
Barnes	B-Company
&	I-Company
Noble	I-Company
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
June	O
22	O
at	O
7	O
PM	O
ET	O
as	O
we	O
welcome	O
six	O
critically	O
acclaimed	O
&	I-Company
bestselling	O
authors	O
--	O
Dhonielle	B-PER
Clayton	E-PER
,	O
Tiffany	B-PER
D.	I-PER
Jackson	E-PER
,	O
Nic	B-PER
Stone	E-PER
,	O
Angie	B-PER
Thomas	E-PER
,	O
Ashley	B-PER
Woodfolk	E-PER
&	I-Company
Nicola	B-PER
Yoon	E-PER
--	O
for	O
a	I-Company
live	O
,	O
virtual	O
block	O
party	O
to	O
celebrate	O
the	O
release	O
of	O
BLACKOUT	O
.	O
Barnes	B-Company
&	I-Company
Noble	I-Company
uses	O
cookies	O
to	O
offer	O
you	O
a	I-Company
better	O
user	O
experience	O
.	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
is	O
the	O
authority	O
on	O
fashion	O
&	O
the	O
go-to	O
retailer	O
for	O
the	O
latest	O
trends	O
,	O
must-have	O
styles	O
&	O
the	O
hottest	O
deals	O
.	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
is	O
your	O
one-stop	O
shop	O
for	O
the	O
latest	O
fashion	O
styles	O
and	O
trends	O
in	O
Women	B-MISC
's	I-MISC
Clothing	I-MISC
!	E-MISC
FOREVER	O
21	I-Company
is	O
a	O
registered	O
trademark	O
,	O
service	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
/	O
or	I-Company
trade	O
name	O
of	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
.	O
All	O
other	O
trademarks	O
,	O
service	O
marks	O
,	O
and	O
trade	O
names	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
Site	S-MISC
are	O
the	O
properties	O
of	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
FOREVER	O
21	I-Company
is	O
a	O
registered	O
trademark	O
,	O
service	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
/	O
or	I-Company
trade	O
name	O
of	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
.	O
All	O
other	O
trademarks	O
,	O
service	O
marks	O
,	O
and	O
trade	O
names	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
Site	S-MISC
are	O
the	O
properties	O
of	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
apologized	O
,	O
stating	O
that	O
the	O
inclusion	O
of	O
the	O
bars	O
was	O
an	O
"	O
oversight	O
.	O
"	O
In	O
September	O
2019	O
,	O
American	S-MISC
singer	O
Ariana	B-PER
Grande	E-PER
accused	O
and	O
sued	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
for	O
$	O
10	O
million	O
for	O
copying	O
her	O
style	O
and	O
likeness	O
by	O
dressing	O
up	O
their	O
models	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
in	O
their	O
photoshoot	O
from	O
her	O
music	O
video	O
of	O
"	O
7	B-MISC
Rings	E-MISC
"	O
.	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
has	O
reached	O
a	O
deal	O
to	O
sell	O
off	O
its	O
assets	O
for	O
$	O
81	O
million	O
,	O
four	O
months	O
after	O
filing	O
for	O
Chapter	B-MISC
11	E-MISC
bankruptcy	O
.	O
FOREVER	O
21	I-Company
is	O
a	O
registered	O
trademark	O
,	O
service	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
/	O
or	I-Company
trade	O
name	O
of	O
Forever	B-Company
21	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
.	O
All	O
other	O
trademarks	O
,	O
service	O
marks	O
,	O
and	O
trade	O
names	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
Site	S-MISC
are	O
the	O
properties	O
of	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
The	O
Chrysler	B-Company
Pacifica	E-MISC
comes	O
equipped	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
standard	O
safety	O
and	O
security	O
features	O
in	O
the	O
industry	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
minivan	O
to	O
offer	O
available	O
all-wheel	O
drive	O
and	O
the	O
Stow	O
‘	O
n	O
Go	O
®	O
Seating	O
and	O
storage	O
system	O
.	O
In	O
addition	O
to	O
the	O
Chrysler	B-Company
brand	O
,	O
Stellantis	B-ORG
North	I-ORG
America	E-ORG
sells	O
vehicles	O
worldwide	O
under	O
the	O
Dodge	S-ORG
,	O
Jeep	S-MISC
,	O
and	O
Ram	O
...	O
The	O
verdict	O
:	O
The	O
2021	O
Chrysler	B-Company
Pacifica	E-MISC
is	O
a	O
lot	O
like	O
my	O
favorite	O
pair	O
of	O
leggings	O
:	O
comfortable	O
,	O
versatile	O
and	O
—	O
with	O
the	O
addition	O
of	O
available	O
all-wheel	O
drive	O
—	O
ready	O
for	O
anything	O
...	O
©	O
2021	O
Chrysler	B-Company
Capital	E-ORG
.	O
Chrysler	B-Company
Capital	E-ORG
is	O
a	O
registered	O
trademark	O
of	O
FCA	B-ORG
US	I-ORG
LLC	E-ORG
and	O
licensed	O
to	O
Santander	B-ORG
Consumer	I-ORG
USA	I-ORG
Inc	E-ORG
.	O
Lease	O
agreements	O
are	O
owned	O
by	O
CCAP	S-ORG
Auto	O
...	O
Dick	B-PER
Hannah	I-PER
Chrysler	B-Company
is	O
a	O
trusted	O
Vancouver	S-LOC
,	O
WA	S-LOC
and	O
Portland	B-ORG
Chrysler	B-Company
Dealer	E-ORG
with	O
800	O
+	O
5-star	O
reviews	O
,	O
New	O
&	O
Used	O
Cars	O
"	O
Believe	B-MISC
in	I-MISC
Nice	E-MISC
"	O
.	O
Dick	B-PER
Hannah	I-PER
Chrysler	B-Company
3517	O
NE	O
Auto	O
Mall	O
Dr.	O
Vancouver	S-LOC
,	O
WA	S-LOC
As	O
your	O
go-to	O
Chrysler	B-Company
,	O
Dodge	S-ORG
,	O
Jeep	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Ram	E-ORG
dealership	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
only	O
sell	O
our	O
customers	O
from	O
West	B-LOC
Fargo	E-LOC
and	O
Moorhead	S-LOC
new	O
vehicles	O
.	O
As	O
a	O
leading	O
Chrysler	B-Company
,	O
Dodge	S-ORG
,	O
Jeep	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Ram	E-ORG
dealer	O
near	O
Chicago	S-LOC
,	O
St.	B-LOC
Charles	I-LOC
CDJR	E-LOC
also	O
has	O
a	O
wide	O
variety	O
of	O
pre-owned	O
cars	O
,	O
trucks	O
,	O
and	O
SUVs	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
choose	O
from	O
.	O
Contact	B-MISC
Fields	I-MISC
Chrysler	B-Company
Jeep	I-MISC
Dodge	I-MISC
RAM	E-MISC
any	O
time	O
by	O
calling	O
our	O
Illinois	S-LOC
dealership	O
at	O
(	O
847	O
)	O
892-6238	O
,	O
or	O
visit	O
us	O
in	O
person	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
vehicles	O
we	O
have	O
in	O
stock	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
test	O
drive	O
at	O
2800	O
Patriot	B-LOC
Blvd	E-LOC
,	O
Glenview	S-LOC
,	O
IL	S-LOC
.	O
©	O
2021	O
Showtime	B-Company
Networks	I-Company
Inc	E-ORG
.	O
SHOWTIME	O
and	O
related	O
marks	O
are	O
trademarks	O
of	O
Showtime	B-Company
Networks	I-Company
Inc.	E-ORG
,	O
a	O
ViacomCBS	B-ORG
Company	E-ORG
.	O
Showtime	B-Company
Networks	I-Company
Inc.	E-ORG
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
entertainment	O
company	O
that	O
oversees	O
the	O
company	O
's	O
premium	O
cable	O
television	O
channels	O
,	O
including	O
its	O
flagship	O
service	O
Showtime	B-Company
.	O
Showtime	B-Company
Networks	I-Company
.	O
Showtimeis	S-ORG
an	O
American	S-MISC
premium	O
televisionnetworkowned	O
by	O
ViacomCBS	B-ORG
Domestic	I-ORG
Media	I-ORG
Networks	I-Company
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
flagship	O
property	O
of	O
parent	O
subsidiary	O
under	O
its	O
Premium	B-ORG
Content	I-ORG
Group	E-ORG
unit	O
,	O
Showtime	B-Company
Networks	I-Company
.	O
In	O
1983	O
,	O
Showtime	B-Company
Networks	I-Company
was	O
formed	O
as	O
Showtime	B-Company
/	O
The	B-ORG
Movie	I-ORG
Channel	E-ORG
,	O
following	O
Viacom	S-ORG
and	O
Warner-Amex	B-ORG
Satellite	I-ORG
Entertainment	E-ORG
(	O
now	O
ViacomCBS	B-ORG
Domestic	I-ORG
Media	I-ORG
Networks	I-Company
)	O
merger	O
of	O
their	O
premium	O
channels	O
,	O
Showtime	B-Company
and	O
The	B-ORG
Movie	I-ORG
Channel	E-ORG
,	O
into	O
a	O
single	O
division	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
world	O
leading	O
Bible	S-MISC
publisher	O
and	O
provider	O
of	O
Christian	S-MISC
communications	O
with	O
over	O
300	O
new	O
,	O
original	O
books	O
and	O
Bibles	S-MISC
published	O
annually	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
world-leading	O
Bible	S-MISC
publisher	O
and	O
provider	O
of	O
Christian	S-MISC
communications	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
HarperCollins	B-ORG
Christian	I-ORG
Publishing	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
,	O
delivers	O
transformational	O
Christian	S-MISC
experiences	O
through	O
its	O
bestselling	O
Bibles	S-MISC
,	O
books	O
,	O
curriculum	O
,	O
academic	O
resources	O
and	O
digital	O
products	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
Divisions	I-ORG
Zondervan	B-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
world-leading	O
Bible	S-MISC
publisher	O
and	O
provider	O
of	O
Christian	S-MISC
communications	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
HarperCollins	B-ORG
Christian	I-ORG
Publishing	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
,	O
delivers	O
transformational	O
Christian	S-MISC
experiences	O
through	O
its	O
bestselling	O
Bibles	S-MISC
,	O
nonfiction	O
,	O
curriculum	O
,	O
academic	O
resources	O
and	O
digital	O
products	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
’s	O
fiction	O
publishing	O
division	O
publishes	O
a	I-Company
range	O
of	O
Amish	S-MISC
,	O
romance	O
...	O
Zondervan	B-Company
is	O
an	I-Company
international	O
Christian	S-MISC
media	O
and	O
publishing	O
company	O
located	O
in	O
Grand	B-LOC
Rapids	E-LOC
,	O
Michigan	S-LOC
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
founding	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Evangelical	B-ORG
Christian	I-ORG
Publishers	I-ORG
Association	E-ORG
(	O
ECPA	S-ORG
)	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
a	I-Company
part	O
of	O
HarperCollins	B-ORG
Christian	I-ORG
Publishing	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
and	O
has	O
multiple	O
imprints	O
including	O
Zondervan	B-Company
Academic	E-ORG
,	O
Zonderkidz	S-ORG
,	O
Blink	S-ORG
,	O
and	O
Editorial	B-ORG
Vida	E-ORG
.	O
...	O
Zondervan	B-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
world	O
leading	O
Bible	S-MISC
publisher	O
and	O
provider	O
of	O
Christian	S-MISC
communications	O
.	O
With	O
over	O
300	O
new	O
,	O
original	O
books	O
and	O
Bibles	S-MISC
published	O
annually	O
,	O
Zondervan	B-Company
has	O
been	O
delivering	O
transformational	O
Christian	S-MISC
experiences	O
through	O
its	O
bestselling	O
Bibles	S-MISC
,	O
books	O
,	O
curricula	O
,	O
academic	O
resources	O
and	O
digital	O
products	O
for	O
more	O
than	O
80	O
years	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
Academic	E-ORG
has	O
been	O
supporting	O
discerning	O
teachers	O
with	O
the	O
highest-quality	O
resources	O
since	O
1931	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
Academic	E-ORG
is	O
the	O
world	O
’s	O
leading	O
Christian	S-MISC
publisher	O
of	O
academic	O
content	O
,	O
trusted	O
by	O
biblical	O
scholars	O
and	O
students	O
of	O
the	O
Word	S-MISC
since	O
1931	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
–	O
ChurchSource	S-ORG
.	O
ChurchSource	S-ORG
is	O
pleased	O
to	O
bring	O
you	O
resources	O
from	O
Zondervan	B-Company
,	O
a	I-Company
world	O
leading	O
Bible	S-MISC
publisher	O
and	O
provider	O
of	O
Christian	S-MISC
communications	O
.	O
Zondervan	B-Company
is	O
the	O
publisher	O
of	O
the	O
New	B-ORG
International	E-ORG
(	O
NIV	S-ORG
)	O
translation	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
home	O
of	O
iconic	O
authors	O
such	O
as	O
Rick	B-PER
Warren	E-PER
,	O
Ann	B-PER
Voskamp	E-PER
,	O
Andy	B-PER
Stanley	E-PER
,	O
Lee	B-PER
Strobel	E-PER
,	O
Joni	B-PER
...	E-PER
France	B-Company
TÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
lÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
visions	I-Company
,	O
the	O
state-owned	O
broadcaster	O
responsible	O
for	O
France	B-Company
2	E-ORG
,	O
France	B-Company
3	E-ORG
,	O
France	B-Company
4	E-ORG
,	O
France	B-Company
5	E-ORG
and	O
RFO	S-ORG
,	O
has	O
extended	O
its	O
long	O
association	O
with	O
Audiopole	S-ORG
and	O
Studer	S-ORG
consoles	O
,	O
by	O
investing	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
two	O
Vista	B-MISC
9	E-MISC
consoles	O
.	O
French	S-MISC
public	O
broadcaster	O
France	B-Company
TÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
lÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
visions	I-Company
is	I-Company
set	O
to	O
launch	O
a	I-Company
redundancy	O
programme	O
as	O
it	O
looks	O
to	O
cut	O
costs	O
.	O
Articles	O
On	O
France	B-Company
TÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
lÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
visions	I-Company
,	O
including	O
:	O
France	B-Company
5	O
,	O
Tv5monde	S-MISC
,	O
France	B-Company
2	O
,	O
France	B-Company
3	O
,	O
RÃ	B-MISC
©	I-Company
seau	I-MISC
France	B-Company
Outre-mer	E-MISC
,	O
France	B-Company
24	O
,	O
List	O
Of	O
Programs	O
Broadcast	O
...	O
2	O
...	O
TF1	S-ORG
,	O
France	B-Company
TÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
lÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
visions	I-Company
and	O
the	O
Canal	B-ORG
+	I-ORG
Group	E-ORG
have	O
reached	O
an	I-Company
agreement	O
over	O
the	O
broadcasting	O
rights	O
to	O
the	O
FIFA	S-ORG
2010	O
World	B-MISC
Cup	E-MISC
.	O
Under	O
this	O
agreement	O
,	O
the	O
TF1	B-ORG
Group	E-ORG
,	O
exclusive	O
holder	O
of	O
the	O
rights	O
to	O
the	O
tournament	O
,	O
will	O
sublicense	O
to	O
France	B-Company
TÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
lÃ	I-Company
©	I-Company
visions	I-Company
and	O
the	O
Canal	B-ORG
+	I-ORG
Group	E-ORG
live	O
broadcast	O
rights	O
to	O
37	O
of	O
the	O
64	O
matches	O
in	O
the	O
competition	O
.	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
comic	O
book	O
publisher	O
and	O
the	O
flagship	O
unit	O
of	O
DC	B-Company
Entertainment	E-ORG
,	O
a	O
subsidiary	O
of	O
the	O
Warner	B-ORG
Bros	E-ORG
.	O
Global	O
Brands	O
and	O
Experiences	O
division	O
of	O
Warner	B-ORG
Bros.	E-ORG
,	O
which	O
itself	O
is	O
a	O
subsidiary	O
of	O
AT	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
T	E-ORG
's	O
WarnerMedia	S-ORG
through	O
its	O
Studios	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
Networks	E-ORG
division	O
.	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
and	O
oldest	O
American	S-MISC
comic	O
book	O
companies	O
.	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
.	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
American	S-MISC
companies	O
in	O
comic	O
books	O
and	O
related	O
media	O
publishing	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
comics	O
publishing	O
branch	O
of	O
DC	B-Company
Entertainment	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Inc.	E-ORG
,	O
a	O
subsidiary	O
of	O
WarnerMedia	S-ORG
(	O
formerly	O
Time	B-ORG
Warner	E-ORG
)	O
,	O
a	O
publishing	O
conglomerate	O
owned	O
by	O
AT	B-ORG
&	I-ORG
T.For	E-ORG
decades	O
,	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
has	O
been	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
largest	O
American	S-MISC
comic	O
book	O
companies	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Marvel	B-ORG
Comics	I-Company
.	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
,	O
American	S-MISC
media	O
and	O
entertainment	O
company	O
whose	O
iconic	O
comic-based	O
properties	O
—	O
such	O
as	O
Batman	S-MISC
,	O
Superman	S-MISC
,	O
Wonder	B-MISC
Woman	E-MISC
,	O
the	O
Flash	S-MISC
,	O
Green	B-ORG
Lantern	E-ORG
,	O
and	O
Aquaman	S-MISC
—	O
represented	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
enduring	O
and	O
recognizable	O
characters	O
in	O
20th	O
-	O
and	O
21st-century	O
popular	O
culture	O
.	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
and	O
oldest	O
American	S-MISC
comic	O
book	O
publishers	O
.	O
DC	B-Company
Comics	I-Company
Database	E-MISC
is	O
a	O
wiki	O
anyone	O
can	O
edit	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
characters	O
(	O
like	O
Superman	S-PER
,	O
Batman	S-MISC
,	O
the	O
Joker	S-MISC
,	O
Catwoman	S-MISC
,	O
and	O
the	O
JLA	S-ORG
)	O
,	O
comic	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
movies	O
!	O
For	O
Papa	B-Company
John	I-Company
's	I-Company
Pizza	I-Company
in	O
Cumberland	S-LOC
,	O
MD	S-LOC
,	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
success	O
is	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
making	O
a	I-Company
great	O
pizza	O
-	O
the	O
more	O
you	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Menu	O
Also	O
Available	O
on	O
Papa	B-Company
John	I-Company
's	I-Company
Pizza	I-Company
Menu	O
*	O
Disclaimer	O
:	O
Information	O
shown	O
on	O
the	O
website	O
may	O
not	O
cover	O
recent	O
changes	O
.	O
For	O
Papa	B-Company
John	I-Company
's	I-Company
Pizza	I-Company
in	O
Pittsburgh	S-LOC
,	O
PA	S-LOC
,	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
success	O
is	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
making	O
a	I-Company
great	O
pizza	O
-	O
the	O
more	O
you	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
Papa	B-Company
John	I-Company
's	I-Company
Pizza	I-Company
in	O
Midland	S-LOC
,	O
MI	S-LOC
,	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
success	O
is	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
making	O
a	I-Company
great	O
pizza	O
-	O
the	O
more	O
you	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Panasonic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
worldwide	O
leader	O
in	O
the	O
development	O
of	O
diverse	O
electronics	O
technologies	O
and	O
solutions	O
for	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
consumer	O
electronics	O
,	O
housing	O
,	O
automotive	O
,	O
enterprise	O
solutions	O
and	O
device	O
industries	O
.	O
Panasonic	B-Company
Corp	I-Company
.	O
Panasonic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
manufactures	O
electric	O
and	O
electronic	O
products	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
forget	O
to	O
visit	O
any	O
of	O
our	O
450	O
+	O
RadioShack	B-Company
locations	O
across	O
America	S-LOC
!	O
RadioShack	B-Company
Non-Contact	O
Forehead	O
Thermometer	O
for	O
Fever	O
Screening	O
.	O
RadioShack	B-Company
,	O
formerly	O
RadioShack	B-Company
Corporation	E-ORG
,	O
is	O
the	O
trade	O
name	O
of	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
retailer	O
founded	O
in	O
1921	O
.	O
In	O
November	O
2020	O
,	O
Retail	B-ORG
Ecommerce	I-ORG
Ventures	E-ORG
(	O
REV	S-ORG
)	O
,	O
a	I-Company
holding	O
company	O
owned	O
by	O
Tai	B-PER
Lopez	E-PER
and	O
Alex	B-PER
Mehr	E-PER
,	O
acquired	O
RadioShack	B-Company
.	O
RadioShack	B-Company
operates	O
primarily	O
as	O
an	O
e-commerce	O
website	O
,	O
a	I-Company
network	O
of	O
approximately	O
500	O
independently	O
owned	O
,	O
franchised	O
RadioShack	B-Company
stores	O
,	O
and	O
a	I-Company
supplier	O
of	O
parts	O
for	O
...	O
RadioShack	B-Company
AM	E-ORG
/	O
FM	O
/	O
WX	B-ORG
Emergency	I-ORG
Crank	I-ORG
Radio	I-Company
with	O
NOAA	B-ORG
Weather	I-ORG
Alert	E-ORG
-	O
Built-in	O
Solar	B-ORG
Panel	E-ORG
,	O
Flashlight	S-ORG
,	O
and	O
USB	B-ORG
Charger	E-ORG
.	O
RadioShack	B-Company
-	O
CLOSED	O
.	O
RadioShack	B-Company
-	O
CLOSED	O
.	O
HobbyTown	S-ORG
-	O
RadioShack	B-Company
Express	E-ORG
in	O
Aurora	S-LOC
.	O
Computer	O
Central	O
-	O
Authorized	O
RadioShack	B-Company
Dealer	E-ORG
in	O
Burlington	S-LOC
.	O
HobbyTown	S-ORG
-	O
RadioShack	B-Company
Express	E-ORG
in	O
Colorado	B-LOC
Springs	E-LOC
.	O
EA	B-Company
Sports	I-Company
is	O
a	O
division	O
of	O
Electronic	B-ORG
Arts	E-ORG
that	O
develops	O
and	O
publishes	O
sports	O
video	O
games	O
.	O
Formerly	O
a	O
marketing	O
gimmick	O
of	O
Electronic	B-ORG
Arts	E-ORG
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
tried	O
to	O
imitate	O
real-life	O
sports	O
networks	O
by	O
calling	O
themselves	O
the	O
"	O
EA	B-Company
Sports	I-Company
Network	E-ORG
"	O
(	O
EASN	S-ORG
)	O
with	O
pictures	O
or	I-Company
endorsements	O
with	O
real	O
commentators	O
such	O
as	O
John	B-PER
Madden	E-PER
,	O
it	O
soon	O
grew	O
up	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
sub-label	O
on	O
its	O
own	O
,	O
releasing	O
game	O
series	O
...	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
newer	O
release	O
in	O
this	O
EA	B-Company
Sports	I-Company
franchise	O
.	O
The	O
American	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Natural	I-Company
History	I-Company
is	I-Company
committed	O
to	I-Company
ensuring	O
that	O
its	O
facilities	O
,	O
exhibitions	O
,	O
and	O
services	O
are	O
accessible	O
to	I-Company
all	O
individuals	O
,	O
including	O
those	O
with	O
disabilities	O
.	O
The	O
American	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Natural	I-Company
History	I-Company
(	O
abbreviated	O
as	O
AMNH	S-ORG
)	O
is	I-Company
a	I-Company
natural	O
history	O
museum	O
on	O
the	O
Upper	B-LOC
West	I-LOC
Side	E-LOC
of	I-Company
Manhattan	S-LOC
,	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
City	E-LOC
.	O
The	O
American	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Natural	I-Company
History	I-Company
is	I-Company
one	O
of	I-Company
the	O
world	O
’s	O
preeminent	O
scientific	O
and	O
cultural	O
institutions	O
.	O
The	O
American	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Natural	I-Company
History	I-Company
,	O
founded	O
in	O
1869	O
,	O
is	I-Company
one	O
of	I-Company
the	O
world	O
’s	O
preeminent	O
scientific	O
,	O
educational	O
,	O
and	O
cultural	O
institutions	O
.	O
After	O
a	I-Company
four-year	O
renovation	O
,	O
the	O
11,000-square-foot	O
Allison	S-PER
and	O
Roberto	B-ORG
Mignone	I-ORG
Halls	I-ORG
of	I-Company
Gems	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Minerals	E-ORG
at	I-Company
the	O
American	B-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Natural	I-Company
History	I-Company
in	O
New	B-LOC
York	E-LOC
will	O
reopen	O
on	O
June	O
12	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
...	O
Find	O
the	O
best	O
books	O
,	O
literary	O
resources	O
and	O
educational	O
solutions	O
for	O
kids	O
at	O
Scholastic	B-Company
,	O
a	I-Company
leader	O
in	O
publishing	O
and	O
education	O
for	O
nearly	O
100	O
years	O
.	O
Scholastic	B-Company
is	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
largest	O
publisher	O
and	O
distributor	O
of	O
children	O
's	O
books	O
,	O
connecting	O
educators	O
and	O
families	O
through	O
accessibility	O
,	O
engagement	O
,	O
and	O
expertise	O
.	O
Over	O
6	O
million	O
students	O
read	O
Scholastic	B-Company
News	E-ORG
every	O
week	O
!	O
Be	O
sure	O
to	O
get	O
permission	O
from	O
a	I-Company
parent	O
or	O
teacher	O
before	O
leaving	O
Scholastic.com	S-MISC
,	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
privacy	O
policy	O
and	O
terms	O
of	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
site	O
you	O
visit	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
Scholastic	B-Company
Learning	I-ORG
Zone	E-ORG
.	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
Company	I-Company
,	O
a	I-Company
leading	O
media	O
company	O
with	O
2007	O
revenues	O
of	O
$	O
3.2	O
billion	O
,	O
includes	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
,	O
the	O
International	B-ORG
Herald	I-ORG
Tribune	E-ORG
,	O
The	B-Company
Boston	I-ORG
Globe	E-ORG
,	O
16	O
other	O
daily	O
newspapers	O
,	O
WQXR-FM	S-ORG
,	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
50	O
Web	O
sites	O
,	O
including	O
NYTimes.com	S-MISC
,	O
Boston.com	S-MISC
,	O
and	O
About.com	S-MISC
.	O
A.G	O
.	O
Sulzberger	S-PER
has	O
been	O
chairman	O
of	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
Company	I-Company
since	O
2021	O
and	O
publisher	O
of	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
since	O
2018	O
.	O
Corporate	O
Governance	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
Company	I-Company
’s	O
ISS	B-ORG
Governance	I-ORG
QualityScore	E-ORG
as	O
of	O
June	O
1	O
,	O
2021	O
is	O
3	O
.	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
Company	I-Company
.	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
Company	I-Company
.	O
Net	O
income	O
attributable	O
to	O
The	B-Company
New	I-Company
York	I-Company
Times	I-Company
Company	I-Company
common	O
stockholders	O
$	O
41,109	O
$	O
32,854	O
25.1	O
%	O
Average	O
number	O
of	O
common	O
shares	O
outstanding	O
:	O
Basic	O
167,647	O
166,549	O
0.7	O
%	O
Diluted	O
...	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
Official	O
Site	O
-	O
Great	O
Deals	O
on	O
TV	I-Company
Packages	O
.	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
.	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
.	O
With	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
,	O
you	O
'll	O
get	O
:	O
TV	I-Company
you	O
can	O
watch	O
live	O
and	O
on	O
demand	O
.	O
The	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
Entertainment	E-ORG
package	O
is	O
our	O
least	O
costly	O
package	O
.	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
support	O
.	O
Contact	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
by	O
chat	O
or	O
phone	O
number	O
.	O
‎	O
Download	O
the	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
app	O
,	O
a	O
companion	O
to	O
your	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
service	O
,	O
and	O
enjoy	O
a	O
world	O
of	O
entertainment	O
.	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
.	O
Download	O
the	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
app	O
,	O
a	O
companion	O
to	O
your	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
service	O
,	O
and	O
enjoy	O
a	O
world	O
of	O
entertainment	O
.	O
Paying	O
your	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
bill	O
is	O
easy	O
and	O
hassle-free	O
.	O
Ordering	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
.	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
Channel	I-ORG
Lineup	I-ORG
Guide	E-ORG
.	O
All	O
of	O
your	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
Account	O
questions	O
…	O
answered	O
!	O
We	O
’ve	O
created	O
this	O
page	O
to	O
offer	O
you	O
a	O
quick	O
way	O
to	O
resolve	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
common	O
DIRECTV	B-Company
Account	O
issues	O
.	O
Visit	O
other	O
sites	O
in	O
the	O
Penguin	B-ORG
Random	B-Company
House	I-Company
Network	E-ORG
.	O
Random	B-Company
House	I-Company
.	O
Bright	O
and	I-Company
Early	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Seuss	S-PER
(	O
Board	B-MISC
Book	E-MISC
)	O
Random	B-Company
House	I-Company
.	O
by	O
Random	B-Company
House	I-Company
,	O
HIT	B-ORG
Entertainment	E-ORG
(	O
2,040	O
)	O
$	O
8.24	O
.	O
Penguin	B-ORG
Random	B-Company
House	I-Company
joins	O
the	O
worldwide	O
publishing	O
and	I-Company
literary	O
community	O
in	O
mourning	O
the	O
sudden	O
passing	O
of	O
M	O
.	O
Richard	B-PER
“	I-PER
Dick	I-PER
”	I-PER
Robinson	I-PER
Jr.	E-PER
,	O
at	O
84	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Penguin	B-MISC
Random	B-Company
House	I-Company
Author	I-MISC
Portal	E-MISC
offers	O
comprehensive	O
information	O
about	O
your	O
titles	O
and	I-Company
a	I-Company
wealth	O
of	O
publishing	O
resources	O
and	I-Company
tips	O
.	O
The	B-Company
Metropolitan	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
.	O
Met	I-Company
Express	O
:	O
Highlights	O
of	I-Company
the	O
Metropolitan	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
in	O
2	O
Hours	O
(	O
From	O
$	O
52.00	O
)	O
Metropolitan	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
Private	O
Guided	O
Tour	O
with	O
Skip-the-Line	O
Ticket	O
(	O
From	O
$	O
100.70	O
)	O
Highlights	O
of	I-Company
the	O
Met	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
Tour	E-MISC
(	O
From	O
$	O
94.69	O
)	O
See	O
all	O
The	B-Company
Metropolitan	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
experiences	O
on	O
Tripadvisor	S-ORG
The	B-Company
Met	I-Company
Store	O
|	O
Gifts	O
from	O
The	B-Company
Metropolitan	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
Opened	O
in	O
1880	O
,	O
The	B-Company
Metropolitan	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
is	O
n’t	O
technically	O
NYC	S-LOC
’s	O
oldest	O
museum	O
(	O
that	O
distinction	O
belongs	O
to	O
The	B-Company
New-York	I-ORG
Historical	I-ORG
Society	E-ORG
,	O
founded	O
in	O
1804	O
)	O
but	O
it	I-Company
is	O
the	O
largest	O
among	O
...	O
The	B-Company
Metropolitan	I-Company
Museum	I-Company
of	I-Company
Art	I-Company
in	O
New	B-LOC
York	E-LOC
has	O
added	O
a	I-Company
bronze	O
plaque	O
recognizing	O
Lenapehoking	S-LOC
,	O
the	O
homeland	O
of	I-Company
the	O
Indigenous	B-MISC
Lenape	E-MISC
diaspora	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
facade	O
of	I-Company
its	O
Fifth	B-LOC
Avenue	E-LOC
building	O
.	O
Scholastic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
multinational	O
publishing	O
,	O
education	O
and	O
media	O
company	O
that	O
publishes	O
and	O
distributes	O
comics	O
,	O
books	O
and	O
educational	O
materials	O
for	O
schools	O
,	O
parents	O
and	O
children	O
.	O
Scholastic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
sells	O
books	O
to	O
children	O
in	O
some	O
165	O
countries	O
.	O
Scholastic	B-Company
Announces	O
The	O
Untimely	O
Death	O
Of	O
Its	O
Chairman	O
And	O
CEO	O
M	O
.	O
Richard	B-PER
(	I-PER
Dick	I-PER
)	I-PER
Robinson	E-PER
,	O
Jr	B-ORG
.	I-ORG
Scholastic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
(	O
NASDAQ	S-ORG
:	O
SCHL	S-ORG
)	O
,	O
the	O
global	O
children	O
's	O
publishing	O
,	O
education	O
and	O
media	O
company	O
...	O
Scholastic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
largest	O
publishers	O
and	O
distributors	O
of	O
children	O
's	O
books	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Sign-in	O
with	O
your	O
Scholastic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
-	O
Prod	S-ORG
account	O
to	O
access	O
Oracle	B-ORG
Transport	I-ORG
Management	E-ORG
(	O
OTM	S-ORG
)	O
Shares	O
of	O
Scholastic	B-Company
Corporation	I-Company
(	O
NASDAQ	S-ORG
:	O
SCHL	S-ORG
)	O
are	O
crashing	O
in	O
early	O
morning	O
trading	O
Friday	O
,	O
down	O
13	O
%	O
as	I-Company
of	O
10	O
a.m	O
.	O
EST	O
after	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
book	O
publisher	O
missed	O
earnings	O
in	O
its	O
second-quarter	O
...	O
Amazon.com	B-Company
.	I-Company
Amazon.com	B-Company
,	I-ORG
Inc	E-ORG
.	I-Company
(/	O
ˈ	O
æ	O
m	I-Company
ə	O
z	I-Company
ɒ	O
n	I-Company
/	O
AM-ə-zon	O
)	O
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
multinational	O
technology	O
company	O
which	O
focuses	O
on	I-Company
e-commerce	O
,	O
cloud	O
computing	O
,	O
digital	O
streaming	O
,	O
and	O
artificial	O
intelligence	O
.	I-Company
Huawei	B-Company
Enterprise	I-ORG
united	I-ORG
States	E-ORG
provides	O
a	I-Company
broad	O
range	O
of	O
innovative	O
ICT	O
infrastructure	O
products	O
and	O
solutions	O
for	O
vertical	O
industry	O
and	O
enterprise	O
customers	O
worldwide	O
.	O
Huawei	B-Company
MateBook	I-MISC
X	O
Pro	O
Signature	O
Edition	O
Thin	O
&	O
Light	O
Laptop	O
,	O
13.9	O
"	O
3K	O
Touch	O
,	O
8th	O
Gen	O
i5-8250U	O
,	O
8	O
GB	O
RAM	O
,	O
256	O
GB	O
SSD	O
,	O
3:2	O
Aspect	O
ratio	O
,	O
Office	O
365	O
Personal	O
Included	O
,	O
Mystic	O
Silver	O
-	O
Mach-W19B	O
.	O
4.2	O
out	O
of	O
5	O
stars	O
.	O
Huawei	B-Company
Has	O
Created	O
a	I-Company
Foundation	O
for	O
Native	O
Batch	O
Computing	O
Platforms	O
.	O
The	O
Huawei	B-Company
P40	I-MISC
Pro	E-MISC
should	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
handset	O
Huawei	B-Company
has	O
ever	O
made	O
.	O
After	O
all	O
,	O
it	O
’s	O
an	O
upgrade	O
on	O
the	O
Huawei	B-Company
P30	I-MISC
Pro	E-MISC
in	O
most	O
ways	O
,	O
with	O
a	I-Company
superb	O
quad-lens	O
camera	O
,	O
phenomenal	O
life	O
from	O
its	O
4	O
...	O
Huawei	B-Company
is	O
China	S-LOC
's	O
—	O
and	O
formerly	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
—	O
largest	O
smartphone	O
vendor	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
the	O
past	O
18	O
months	O
,	O
it	O
learned	O
an	O
important	O
lesson	O
:	O
the	O
company	O
ca	O
n't	O
rely	O
on	O
the	O
US	S-LOC
supply	O
chain	O
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
to	O
invest	O
in	I-Company
new	O
studio	O
and	O
its	O
current	O
project	O
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
(	O
SIE	S-ORG
)	O
,	O
formerly	O
known	O
as	O
Sony	B-Company
Computer	I-ORG
Entertainment	I-Company
(	O
SCE	S-ORG
)	O
,	O
is	O
a	I-Company
multinational	O
video	O
game	O
and	O
digital	O
entertainment	O
company	O
wholly	O
owned	O
by	O
multinational	O
conglomerate	O
Sony	B-Company
Group	I-ORG
Corporation	E-ORG
.	O
The	O
SIE	B-ORG
Group	E-ORG
is	O
made	O
up	O
of	O
two	O
legal	O
corporate	O
entities	O
:	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
LLC	E-ORG
(	O
SIE	B-ORG
LLC	E-ORG
)	O
based	O
in	I-Company
San	B-LOC
Mateo	E-LOC
,	O
California	S-LOC
,	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
,	O
and	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
...	O
About	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
.	O
Recognized	O
as	O
a	I-Company
global	O
leader	O
in	I-Company
interactive	O
and	O
digital	O
entertainment	O
,	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
(	O
SIE	S-ORG
)	O
is	O
responsible	O
for	O
the	O
PlayStation	B-ORG
®	E-ORG
brand	O
and	O
family	O
of	O
products	O
and	O
services	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	I-Company
list	O
of	O
video	O
games	O
published	O
by	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
,	O
formerly	O
known	O
as	O
Sony	B-Company
Computer	I-ORG
Entertainment	I-Company
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
.	O
[	O
Tokyo	S-LOC
,	O
February	O
12	O
,	O
2019	O
/	O
San	B-LOC
Mateo	E-LOC
,	O
California	S-LOC
,	O
February	O
11	O
,	O
2019	O
]	O
-	O
Sony	B-Company
Corporation	E-ORG
and	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
(	O
SIE	S-ORG
)	O
today	O
announced	O
that	O
SIE	S-ORG
Deputy	O
President	O
Jim	B-PER
Ryan	E-PER
will	O
be	O
appointed	O
President	O
and	O
CEO	O
of	O
SIE	S-ORG
effective	O
April	O
1	O
,	O
2019	O
.	O
Jim	B-PER
Ryan	E-PER
President	O
&	O
CEO	O
,	O
Sony	B-Company
Interactive	I-Company
Entertainment	I-Company
Date	O
published	O
:	O
February	O
23	O
,	O
2021	O
199	O
1,254	O
.	O
Find	O
content	O
from	O
your	O
favorite	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
networks	O
!	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
Media	E-ORG
,	O
LLC	S-ORG
is	O
an	O
American	S-MISC
mass	O
media	O
and	O
entertainment	O
conglomerate	O
owned	O
by	O
Comcast	S-ORG
and	O
headquartered	O
at	O
30	O
Rockefeller	B-ORG
Plaza	E-ORG
in	O
Midtown	B-LOC
Manhattan	E-LOC
,	O
New	B-LOC
York	I-LOC
City.	E-LOC
.	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
is	O
primarily	O
involved	O
in	O
the	O
media	O
and	O
entertainment	O
industry	O
.	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
owns	O
and	O
operates	O
a	I-Company
valuable	O
portfolio	O
of	O
news	O
and	O
entertainment	O
television	O
networks	O
,	O
a	I-Company
premier	O
motion	O
picture	O
company	O
,	O
significant	O
television	O
production	O
operations	O
,	O
a	I-Company
leading	O
television	O
stations	O
group	O
,	O
world-renowned	O
theme	O
parks	O
,	O
and	O
a	I-Company
premium	O
ad-supported	O
streaming	O
service	O
.	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
is	O
a	I-Company
subsidiary	O
of	O
Comcast	B-ORG
Corporation	E-ORG
.	O
Peacock	S-ORG
is	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
’s	O
streaming	O
service	O
.	O
Peacock	S-ORG
is	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
’s	O
streaming	O
service	O
.	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
owns	O
and	O
operates	O
a	I-Company
valuable	O
portfolio	O
of	O
news	O
and	O
entertainment	O
television	O
networks	O
,	O
a	I-Company
premier	O
motion	O
picture	O
company	O
,	O
significant	O
television	O
production	O
operations	O
,	O
a	I-Company
leading	O
television	O
stations	O
group	O
,	O
world-renowned	O
theme	O
parks	O
,	O
and	O
a	I-Company
suite	O
of	O
leading	O
Internet-based	O
businesses	O
.	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
News	I-ORG
Group	E-ORG
is	O
the	O
news	O
division	O
of	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
,	O
composed	O
of	O
the	O
NBC	I-Company
News	E-ORG
,	O
CNBC	S-ORG
and	O
MSNBC	S-ORG
units	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
created	O
on	O
July	O
19	O
,	O
2012	O
under	O
chairwoman	O
Pat	B-PER
Fili-Krushel	E-PER
.	O
In	O
April	O
2015	O
,	O
Andrew	B-PER
Lack	E-PER
took	O
over	O
as	O
CEO	O
of	O
the	O
group	O
,	O
with	O
CNBC	S-ORG
being	O
moved	O
to	O
a	I-Company
direct	O
unit	O
reporting	O
to	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
CEO	O
.	O
Life	O
at	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
.	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
CEO	O
Steve	B-PER
Burke	E-PER
will	O
retire	O
on	O
August	O
14	O
,	O
2020	O
following	O
the	O
Summer	B-MISC
Olympics	E-MISC
in	O
Tokyo	S-LOC
,	O
Comcast	S-ORG
announced	O
on	O
Monday	O
.	O
Jeff	B-PER
Shell	E-PER
will	O
become	O
CEO	O
of	O
NBCUniversal	B-Company
beginning	O
Jan.	O
1	O
,	O
2020	O
...	O
At	O
Unilever	B-Company
we	O
meet	O
everyday	O
needs	O
for	O
nutrition	O
,	O
hygiene	O
and	O
personal	O
care	O
with	O
brands	O
that	O
help	O
people	O
feel	O
good	O
,	O
look	O
good	O
and	O
get	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
life	O
.	O
Unilever	B-Company
is	O
recognized	O
as	O
the	O
No	O
.	O
Unilever	B-Company
Takes	O
Action	O
to	O
Create	O
Systemic	O
Change	O
for	O
LGBTQI	O
+	O
Communities	O
.	O
Unilever	B-Company
products	O
include	O
food	O
,	O
condiments	O
,	O
ice	O
cream	O
,	O
wellbeing	O
vitamins	O
,	O
minerals	O
and	O
supplements	O
,	O
tea	O
,	O
coffee	O
,	O
breakfast	O
cereal	O
,	O
cleaning	O
agents	O
,	O
water	O
and	O
air	O
purifiers	O
,	O
pet	O
food	O
,	O
toothpaste	O
,	O
beauty	O
products	O
,	O
and	O
personal	O
care	O
.	O
Unilever	B-Company
is	O
the	O
largest	O
producer	O
of	O
soap	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Unilever	B-Company
makes	O
and	O
sells	O
products	O
under	O
more	O
than	O
1,000	O
brand	O
names	O
worldwide	O
.	O
At	O
Unilever	B-Company
,	O
you	O
’re	O
much	O
more	O
than	O
your	O
job	O
title	O
.	O
Unilever	B-Company
is	O
the	O
first	O
company	O
to	O
voluntarily	O
put	O
a	O
climate	O
transition	O
action	O
plan	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
shareholder	O
vote	O
.	O
Unilever	B-Company
-	O
Raeford	S-LOC
,	O
North	B-LOC
Carolina	E-LOC
,	O
Raeford	S-LOC
,	O
North	B-LOC
Carolina	E-LOC
.	O
About	O
Unilever	B-Company
.	O
As	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
third-largest	O
provider	O
of	O
consumer	O
goods	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
likely	O
that	O
Unilever	B-Company
manufactures	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
products	O
you	O
already	O
use	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Explore	O
Audi	B-Company
electric	O
models	O
.	O
Our	O
current	O
e-tron	O
lineup	O
is	O
the	O
just	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
how	O
we	O
see	O
the	O
future	O
of	O
electric	O
at	O
Audi	B-Company
.	O
Discover	O
your	O
Audi	B-Company
electric	O
or	O
hybrid	O
model	O
.	O
Discover	B-ORG
Audi	B-Company
as	O
a	O
brand	O
,	O
company	O
and	O
employer	O
on	O
our	O
international	O
website	O
.	O
For	O
highly	O
qualified	O
customers	O
through	O
Audi	B-Company
Financial	I-ORG
Services	E-ORG
.	O
Audi	B-Company
Indianapolis	E-ORG
.	O
Audi	B-Company
Bellevue	E-ORG
has	O
a	O
wide	O
range	O
of	O
pre-owned	O
Audi	B-Company
models	O
available	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
Certified	O
Pre-Owned	O
.	O
In	O
addition	O
to	O
pre-owned	O
Audi	B-Company
vehicles	O
,	O
we	O
also	O
carry	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
used	O
cars	O
,	O
trucks	O
,	O
and	O
SUVs	O
from	O
other	O
premium	O
manufacturers	O
.	O
Visit	O
us	O
today	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
test	O
drive	O
in	O
your	O
dream	O
Audi	B-Company
!	E-MISC
You	O
will	O
find	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
popular	O
new	O
Audi	B-Company
cars	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
new	O
A6	O
,	O
A4	O
,	O
S4	O
,	O
R8	O
,	O
Q8	O
,	O
e-tron	O
and	O
much	O
more	O
.	O
Best	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
our	O
Audi	B-Company
dealership	O
is	O
conveniently	O
located	O
a	O
short	O
drive	O
from	O
Birmingham	S-LOC
,	O
in	O
Irondale	S-LOC
.	O
Audi	B-Company
also	O
offers	O
an	O
ever-growing	O
selection	O
of	O
hybrid	O
and	O
electric	O
vehicles	O
(	O
EVs	O
)	O
.	O
Just	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Audi	B-Company
A7	E-MISC
e	O
sportback	O
sedan	O
and	O
Q5	O
e	O
crossover	O
SUV	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
which	O
offer	O
plug-in	O
capability	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
there	O
's	O
the	O
e-tron	O
,	O
Audi	B-Company
's	O
first-ever	O
zero-emissions	O
car	O
.	O
Helpful	O
Audi	B-Company
Finance	O
Assistance	O
We	O
understand	O
that	O
shopping	O
for	O
a	O
new	O
auto	O
loan	O
or	O
lease	O
for	O
your	O
Audi	B-Company
purchase	O
can	O
be	O
unnecessarily	O
confusing	O
and	O
tedious	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Nashville	S-LOC
dealership	O
provides	O
you	O
with	O
an	O
excellent	O
alternative	O
.	O
Through	O
our	O
Audi	B-Company
financing	O
department	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
complete	O
a	O
single	O
application	O
and	O
put	O
our	O
team	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Kansas	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
Audi	B-Company
is	O
a	O
luxury	O
Audi	B-Company
dealership	O
with	O
new	O
and	O
used	O
inventory	O
along	O
with	O
finance	O
options	O
and	O
a	O
comprehensive	O
Service	O
/	O
Parts	O
Department	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
Collision	O
Center	O
.	O
Portland	B-ORG
Oregon	E-ORG
's	O
Premier	B-ORG
Audi	B-Company
Dealership	E-ORG
.	O
Audi	B-Company
Beaverton	E-LOC
is	O
located	O
in	O
Portland	S-LOC
,	O
Oregon	S-LOC
's	O
quiet	O
neighborhood	O
of	O
Beaverton	S-LOC
that	O
is	O
just	O
minutes	O
away	O
with	O
parks	O
,	O
recreation	O
,	O
and	O
hosts	O
large	O
companies	O
like	O
Nike	S-ORG
,	O
Tektronix	S-ORG
and	O
Intel	S-ORG
.	O
Portland	S-LOC
's	O
Premier	B-ORG
Audi	B-Company
Dealer	E-ORG
has	O
special	O
sale	O
and	O
lease	O
offers	O
on	O
all	O
new	O
Audi	B-Company
Cars	O
&	O
SUVs	O
;	O
including	O
the	O
A3	O
,	O
A4	O
,	O
A5	O
,	O
A6	O
,	O
Q3	O
,	O
Q5	O
,	O
and	O
Q7	O
.	O
The	O
Museum	B-Company
of	I-Company
Fine	I-Company
Arts	I-Company
,	I-Company
Boston	I-Company
,	I-Company
is	O
one	O
of	I-Company
the	O
most	O
comprehensive	O
art	O
museums	O
in	I-Company
the	O
world	O
with	O
a	O
collection	O
that	O
exemplifies	O
the	O
breadth	O
,	I-Company
richness	O
,	I-Company
and	O
diversity	O
of	I-Company
artistic	O
expression	O
,	I-Company
from	O
prehistoric	O
times	O
to	I-Company
modern	O
day	O
.	O
Museum	B-Company
gifts	O
are	O
always	O
appreciated	O
,	I-Company
and	O
the	O
Museum	B-Company
of	I-Company
Fine	I-Company
Arts	I-Company
,	I-Company
Boston	I-Company
has	O
something	O
beautiful	O
for	O
every	O
one	O
's	O
life	O
.	O
Culver	B-ORG
City	I-ORG
CA	E-ORG
–	O
June	O
1	O
,	O
2021	O
–	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Television	E-ORG
(	O
SP	S-ORG
.	O
Disney	S-ORG
and	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	E-ORG
Announce	O
Unprecedented	O
Post-Pay	O
1	O
Content	O
Licensing	O
Agreement	O
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	I-ORG
Inc	E-ORG
.	O
The	O
official	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Releasing	I-ORG
International	E-ORG
website	O
listing	O
country	O
portal	O
and	O
gateway	O
pages	O
.	O
The	O
long	O
awaited	O
latest	O
from	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Animation	E-ORG
,	O
The	B-ORG
Mitchells	E-ORG
vs.	O
the	B-ORG
Machines	E-ORG
is	O
set	O
to	O
make	O
its	O
streaming	O
premiere	O
on	I-Company
Netflix	S-ORG
on	I-Company
April	O
30	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Studio	I-MISC
Tour	E-MISC
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Television	I-ORG
Login	I-ORG
Menu	E-ORG
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Classics	E-ORG
is	O
an	O
autonomous	O
division	O
of	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
Entertainment	E-ORG
founded	O
in	O
January	O
1992	O
that	O
distributes	O
,	O
produces	O
and	O
acquires	O
independent	O
films	O
from	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
and	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Sony	B-Company
Pictures	I-Company
-	O
Sony	B-Company
Redeem	O
...	O
Loading	O
...	O
Toshiba	B-Company
provides	O
innovative	O
and	O
cost	O
efficient	O
b2b	O
solutions	O
for	O
multiple	O
industries	O
servicing	O
the	O
industrial	O
,	O
power	O
and	O
energy	O
,	O
and	O
retail	O
verticals	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
Toshiba	B-Company
's	O
global	O
website	O
.	O
This	O
website	O
provides	O
Information	O
about	O
Toshiba	B-Company
.	O
Toshiba	B-Company
Group	E-ORG
aims	O
to	O
become	O
an	O
even	O
stronger	O
global	O
contender	O
by	O
unleashing	O
our	O
powers	O
of	O
imagination	O
to	O
anticipate	O
,	O
ahead	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
capitalize	O
on	O
the	O
coming	O
trends	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
business	O
environment	O
.	O
Toshiba	B-Company
TVs	E-ORG
offer	O
innovative	O
features	O
and	O
exceptional	O
performance	O
without	O
premium	O
prices	O
.	O
Toshiba	B-Company
was	O
founded	O
in	O
1939	O
as	O
Tokyo	B-ORG
Shibaura	I-ORG
Denki	I-ORG
K.K	E-ORG
.	O
(	O
Tokyo	B-ORG
Shibaura	I-ORG
Electric	I-ORG
Co.	E-ORG
,	O
Ltd	S-ORG
)	O
through	O
the	O
merger	O
of	O
Shibaura	B-ORG
Seisaku-sho	E-ORG
(	O
founded	O
in	O
1875	O
)	O
and	O
Tokyo	B-ORG
Denki	E-ORG
(	O
founded	O
in	O
1890	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
company	O
name	O
was	O
officially	O
changed	O
to	O
Toshiba	B-Company
Corporation	E-ORG
in	O
1978	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
Toshiba	B-Company
Electronic	I-ORG
Devices	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Storage	I-ORG
Corporation	E-ORG
's	O
website	O
.	O
Toshiba	B-Company
Electronic	I-ORG
Devices	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Storage	I-ORG
Corporation	E-ORG
supplies	O
a	I-Company
broad	O
range	O
of	O
market-leading	O
product	O
lines	O
to	O
the	O
world	O
by	O
fully	O
utilizing	O
its	O
leading-edge	O
development	O
and	O
technological	O
capabilities	O
together	O
with	O
its	O
sophisticated	O
manufacturing	O
...	O
Find	O
and	O
download	O
Toshiba	B-Company
drivers	O
and	O
manuals	O
for	O
your	O
Toshiba	B-Company
MFPs	E-MISC
,	O
thermal	O
barcode	O
and	O
label	O
printers	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
Visit	O
our	O
Toshiba	B-Company
Support	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Toshiba	B-Company
printer	O
drivers	O
,	O
guides	O
,	O
manuals	O
,	O
tutorials	O
,	O
troubleshooting	O
help	O
and	O
more	O
for	O
our	O
line-up	O
of	O
MFPs	O
,	O
office	O
printers	O
,	O
office	O
copiers	O
,	O
thermal	O
barcode	O
printers	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
of	I-ORG
Art	E-ORG
serves	O
the	O
nation	O
by	O
welcoming	O
all	I-Company
people	O
to	O
explore	O
and	O
experience	O
art	O
,	O
creativity	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
shared	O
humanity	O
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
of	I-ORG
Art	E-ORG
is	O
located	O
on	I-Company
the	O
National	I-Company
Mall	E-LOC
between	O
3rd	O
and	O
9th	B-LOC
Streets	I-LOC
NW	E-LOC
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
is	O
an	O
art	O
museum	O
in	O
Trafalgar	B-LOC
Square	E-LOC
in	O
the	O
City	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Westminster	E-LOC
,	O
in	O
Central	B-LOC
London	E-LOC
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
,	O
London	S-LOC
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
of	I-ORG
London	E-ORG
Guided	O
Museum	O
Tour	O
-	O
Private	O
Tour	O
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
of	I-ORG
Art	E-ORG
,	O
and	O
its	O
attached	O
Sculpture	B-ORG
Garden	E-ORG
,	O
is	O
a	I-Company
national	O
art	O
museum	O
in	O
Washington	B-LOC
,	I-LOC
D.C.	E-LOC
,	O
located	O
on	I-Company
the	O
National	I-Company
Mall	E-LOC
,	O
between	O
3rd	O
and	O
9th	B-LOC
Streets	E-LOC
,	O
at	I-Company
Constitution	B-LOC
Avenue	I-LOC
NW	E-LOC
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
closed	O
temporarily	O
in	O
January	O
of	O
2019	O
,	O
to	O
facilitate	O
the	O
move	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
National	I-Company
Museum	E-ORG
opening	O
in	O
2022	O
.	O
The	B-Company
National	I-Company
Gallery	I-Company
will	O
remain	O
a	I-Company
part	O
of	O
the	O
National	I-Company
Museum	E-ORG
and	O
continue	O
to	O
exhibit	O
art	O
in	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Official	O
website	O
of	O
the	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
,	O
the	O
world	O
's	O
largest	O
museum	O
and	O
research	O
complex	O
,	O
with	O
19	O
museums	O
,	O
9	O
research	O
centers	O
,	O
and	O
affiliates	O
around	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Journeys	I-MISC
A	I-MISC
Danube	I-MISC
River	I-MISC
Cruise	E-MISC
From	O
the	O
Czech	B-LOC
Republic	E-LOC
and	O
Germany	S-LOC
to	O
Bulgaria	S-LOC
Smithsonian	B-Company
Journeys	O
The	O
Emerald	B-LOC
Isle	I-LOC
Uncover	I-LOC
Ireland	E-LOC
's	O
many	O
charms	O
,	O
from	O
lively	O
Dublin	S-LOC
to	O
the	O
Aran	B-LOC
Islands	E-LOC
and	O
Ring	B-LOC
of	I-LOC
Kerry	E-LOC
.	O
At	O
the	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
.	O
Smithsonianmag.com	S-MISC
places	O
a	I-Company
Smithsonian	B-Company
lens	O
on	I-Company
the	O
world	O
,	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
topics	O
and	O
subject	O
matters	O
researched	O
,	O
studied	O
and	O
exhibited	O
by	O
the	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	E-ORG
--	O
science	O
,	O
history	O
,	O
art	O
...	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
’s	O
collection	O
of	O
museums	O
serve	O
as	O
a	I-Company
treasure	O
chest	O
for	O
visitors	O
to	O
DC	S-LOC
.	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Channel	E-ORG
offers	O
powerful	O
documentaries	O
and	O
shows	O
exploring	O
history	O
,	O
science	O
,	O
nature	O
,	O
aviation	O
,	O
space	O
and	O
pop	O
culture	O
.	O
Learn	O
more	O
about	O
the	O
operating	O
status	O
of	O
all	O
other	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
museums	O
at	O
si.edu	O
/	O
visit	O
.	O
The	O
Smithsonian	B-Company
Institution	E-ORG
(/	O
s	I-Company
m	I-Company
ɪ	O
θ	O
ˈ	O
s	I-Company
oʊ	O
n	I-Company
i	I-Company
ə	O
n	I-Company
/	O
smith-SOH-nee-ən	O
)	O
,	O
also	O
known	O
simply	O
as	O
The	B-ORG
Smithsonian	B-Company
,	O
is	O
a	I-Company
trust	O
instrumentality	O
of	O
the	O
United	B-LOC
States	E-LOC
composed	O
as	O
a	I-Company
group	O
of	O
museums	O
and	O
research	O
centers	O
.	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
Infotainment	E-MISC
3	O
System	O
functionality	O
varies	O
by	O
model	O
.	O
Research	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
Models	O
Featured	O
New	O
Vehicles	O
Showroom	O
Business	O
Elite	O
Reserve	O
the	O
All-New	B-MISC
Chevy	I-MISC
Bolt	I-MISC
EUV	I-MISC
The	I-MISC
Chevrolet	B-Company
Electric	I-MISC
Future	I-MISC
Popular	I-MISC
Models	E-MISC
.	O
2021	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
Silverado	I-MISC
1500	E-MISC
2021	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
Equinox	E-MISC
2021	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
Trax	I-MISC
2021	I-MISC
Chevrolet	B-Company
Colorado	I-MISC
Work	I-MISC
Trucks	I-MISC
The	I-MISC
Chevrolet	B-Company
Silverado	I-MISC
4500	I-MISC
Fleet	I-MISC
Vans	I-MISC
City	I-MISC
Express	I-MISC
Express	I-MISC
Commercial	I-MISC
Cutaway	E-MISC
Capital	B-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
in	O
Wake	B-LOC
Forest	I-LOC
Serving	I-LOC
Raleigh	E-LOC
,	O
Durham	S-LOC
and	O
Chapel	B-LOC
Hill	E-LOC
,	O
NC	S-LOC
.	O
Located	O
near	O
Raleigh	S-LOC
,	O
NC	S-LOC
,	O
Capital	B-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
is	O
the	O
premier	O
dealer	O
for	O
new	O
and	O
pre-owned	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
vehicles	O
in	O
Wake	B-LOC
Forest	E-LOC
,	O
North	B-LOC
Carolina	E-LOC
.	O
Customer	O
satisfaction	O
is	O
the	O
number	O
one	O
priority	O
of	O
the	O
dedicated	O
professionals	O
at	O
Capital	B-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
.	O
For	O
over	O
24	O
years	O
,	O
Henderson	B-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
Co.	E-ORG
has	O
been	O
your	O
dealer	O
of	O
choice	O
for	O
your	O
new	O
and	O
quality	O
pre-owned	O
vehicles	O
,	O
including	O
top-quality	O
auto	O
service	O
.	O
Rick	B-ORG
Hendrick	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
is	O
your	O
trusted	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
dealership	O
in	O
Charlotte	S-LOC
and	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
our	O
loyal	O
customers	O
keep	O
coming	O
back	O
.	O
Montgomery	B-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
is	O
more	O
than	O
just	O
a	O
new	O
and	O
used	O
vehicle	O
source	O
.	O
Our	O
car	O
parts	O
and	O
auto	O
service	O
center	O
provides	O
genuine	O
components	O
,	O
tires	O
,	O
and	O
quality	O
maintenance	O
to	O
all	O
Louisville	S-LOC
,	O
Shepherdsville	S-LOC
,	O
and	O
Lexington	B-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
customers	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
Green	B-ORG
Family	I-ORG
Chevrolet	B-Company
.	O
John	B-PER
Elway	I-PER
Chevrolet	B-Company
is	O
the	O
#	O
1	O
Chevy	B-ORG
Dealer	E-ORG
in	O
Colorado	S-LOC
8	O
years	O
in	O
a	O
row	O
.	O
We	O
offer	O
Chevrolet	B-Company
new	O
,	O
used	O
vehicles	O
,	O
certified	O
pre-owned	O
,	O
parts	O
,	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
body	O
shop	O
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
is	O
dedicated	O
to	O
fostering	O
an	O
inclusive	O
culture	O
that	O
empowers	O
the	O
LGBTQIA	S-ORG
+	O
community	O
—	O
both	O
at	O
our	O
company	O
and	O
beyond	O
—	O
in	O
its	O
pursuit	O
of	O
equal	O
rights	O
and	O
unquestioned	O
acceptance	O
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
G923	I-MISC
Racing	I-MISC
Wheel	I-MISC
and	I-MISC
Pedals	I-MISC
Features	I-MISC
New	I-MISC
Force	I-MISC
Feedback	I-MISC
System	E-MISC
,	O
Delivering	O
Next-Generation	O
Realism	O
and	O
Performance	O
for	O
Sim	B-MISC
Racers	I-MISC
Logitech	B-Company
G	E-MISC
,	O
a	O
brand	O
of	O
Logitech	B-Company
,	O
(	O
SIX	S-ORG
:	O
LOGN	S-ORG
)	O
(	O
NASDAQ	S-MISC
:	O
LOGI	S-ORG
)	O
and	O
leading	O
innovator	O
of	O
gaming	O
technologies	O
and	O
gear	O
,	O
today	O
unveiled	O
the	O
Logitech	B-Company
G923	E-MISC
Racing	O
Wheel	O
and	O
Pedals	O
,	O
a	O
high	O
performance	O
racing	O
wheel	O
that	O
revolutionizes	O
the	O
sim	O
racing	O
experience	O
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
Keyboard	E-ORG
,	O
Presentation	O
and	O
Mice	O
Software	O
-	O
macOS	O
11	O
(	O
Big	O
Sur	O
)	O
Compatibility	O
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
Options	E-ORG
permission	O
prompts	O
on	O
macOS	O
Big	B-MISC
Sur	E-MISC
,	O
macOS	O
Catalina	S-MISC
,	O
and	O
macOS	O
Mojave	S-LOC
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
Presentation	E-ORG
permission	O
prompts	O
on	O
macOS	O
BigSur	S-MISC
.	O
Important	O
information	O
for	O
Logitech	B-Company
Control	I-ORG
Center	E-ORG
and	O
macOS	B-ORG
Catalina	E-ORG
and	O
Mojave	S-LOC
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
Amazon	I-ORG
Store	E-ORG
.	O
Shop	O
Logitech	B-Company
mice	O
and	O
keyboards	O
Disclosures	O
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
Options	E-ORG
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
G	O
HUB	O
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
G502	I-MISC
HERO	I-MISC
High	I-MISC
Performance	I-MISC
Gaming	I-MISC
Mouse	E-MISC
(	O
910-005469	O
)	O
Maximum	O
dpi	O
:	O
16000	O
dpi	O
Hand	O
Orientation	O
:	O
Right	O
Hand	O
Mouse	O
Adjustable	O
Weight	O
:	O
5	O
x	O
3.6g	O
Operating	O
System	O
Supported	O
:	O
Windows	O
7	O
or	O
later	O
macOS	O
10.11	O
or	O
later	O
Chrome	O
OS	O
Model	O
#	O
:	O
910-005469	O
Item	O
#	O
:	O
3C6-0064-00002	O
Return	O
Policy	O
:	O
Standard	O
Return	O
Policy	O
Logitech	B-Company
G	I-ORG
HUB	E-ORG
gives	O
you	O
a	O
single	O
portal	O
for	O
optimizing	O
and	O
customizing	O
all	O
your	O
supported	O
Logitech	B-Company
G	E-MISC
gear	O
:	O
mice	O
,	O
keyboards	O
,	O
headsets	O
,	O
speakers	O
,	O
and	O
webcams	O
.	O
Logitech	B-Company
Harmony	E-MISC
remote	O
controls	O
are	O
easy	O
to	O
setup	O
,	O
easy	O
to	O
use	O
,	O
support	O
270,000	O
+	O
devices	O
from	O
6,000	O
+	O
brands	O
.	O
CATechUSA	S-ORG
(	O
CA	B-Company
Technologies	I-Company
USA	E-ORG
,	O
LLC	S-ORG
)	O
is	O
a	O
Tennessee	B-ORG
Limited	I-ORG
Liability	I-ORG
Company	E-ORG
owned	O
and	O
operated	O
by	O
Eric	S-PER
and	O
Whitney	B-PER
Ballard	E-PER
.	O
CA	B-Company
Technologies	I-Company
story	O
began	O
in	O
2011	O
when	O
we	O
stepped	O
in	O
the	O
technology	O
consulting	O
with	O
passion	O
and	O
education	O
in	O
technology	O
in	O
a	O
desire	O
to	O
improve	O
the	O
operational	O
efficiencies	O
of	O
the	O
technology	O
fitouts	O
within	O
the	O
financial	O
market	O
participants	O
.	O
CA	B-Company
Technologies	I-Company
Infrastructure	I-ORG
Software	E-ORG
.	O
CA	B-Company
Technologies	I-Company
HVLP	O
